Subtitle source: Chihiro
https://nyaa.si/view/1847496
I love
myself.
What's wrong with that?
Are you jealous?
Am I an eyesore? Am I strange?
I won't even read
those replies.
Wearing my favorite clothes,
and my favorite makeup,
and my usual half twin tails,
I'm heading out!
I've got my parasol. Even if I'm by myself,
I'm the happiest!
Chu! Sorry I'm so cute. Sorry I was born this way.
Chu! Sorry I'm so flirty.
Does it bother you? So sorry.
Does it make you mad? Too bad.
I might have
different interests.
You might think I'm odd
and make fun of me.
But I'm not gonna bend.
I'm not afraid
of the likes of you.
I'm my own ally.
I make myself my top priority.
I won't let pointless trifles bother me.
That's who I am.
Chu! Sorry I'm so cute. Sorry I worked for it.
Chu! Sorry I'm so precious.
Sorry my feminine wiles are so strong.
Does it make you mad? Too bad.