Subtitles: DeerGod
Alternative subtitles are available
Switch to English (United States) to view them
This is a work of fiction. All the characters, places, and businesses shown are fictitious. Any resemblance to reality is purely coincidental.
These fair maidens who flock
to the garden of Fudou Myou-ou,
smiles as spotless
as those of Shinsengumi soldiers,
once again cross the banks
of the Tama River.
Their unsullied bodies and hearts
clad in school uniforms of pure white.
Taking care not to ruffle
the pleats of their skirts...
...or dishevel their blue sailor collars,
they walk slowly,
as dictated by local customs.
Tokyo Metropolitan Hinominami High School...
A true garden of maidens.
(Addendum: It's co-ed.)
Good morning, dear viewers!
Deer!
Deer, deer, deer!
Nyun
Shikanoko's doe-eyed nonchalance, Koshi-tan's tale of vigilance
Shikanoko's doe-eyed nonchalance, Koshi-tan's tale of vigilance (nyun nyun)
Doe eyes popping up here and there without a care
Antlers jamming out, and the body of a girl?!
It's the craze that's in the latest rumors
Let's see what you can do, greenhorn!
"They've been found in Japan since ancient times."
Deer crackers? I'll take a lifetime supply!
Reindeer are comrades, wild goats are bovines
but together, we're all even-toed ungulates!
Gracefully dancing the nyun step...
Until the dawn breaks!
One, two, three!
Even with a life of ruminating, nyunyunyun
you can never predict deer-tinted days!
Avant-garde is perfect, the chaos will only deepen!
You'll get hooked before you know it, nyunyunyun
on the chaos & nonsense, deer-tinted days!
Bring on the unprecedented!
Anything goes, there's no rules here
Your smile always fills me with energy
Could you be m-m-my promised deer?!
With my vigilance hidden deep in my heart
I want to be with you forever!
Shikanoko's doe-eyed nonchalance, Koshi-tan's tale of vigilance!
GIRL MEETS DEER
It's still so cold out today!
Rained yesterday, too.
Be careful not to slip.
Are you okay?
Ah! Umm...
Thank you so much!
You're welcome.
Koshi Torako,
a second-year at Hinominami High.
President of the student council,
and class rep for class 2-B.
Not to mention... a stunning beauty, a student with
outstanding grades, and a well-rounded athlete.
Miss High School
2nd Semester Finals   Top 50
1: Koshi Torako, 500
2: Nekoyamada Neko, 499
3: Kitsunezaka Tsune, 490
4: Komai Koma, 489
5: Todaya Uta, 485
6: Kumagai Kuma, 480
The quintessential perfect girl,
whether at school or around town.
She's wonderful!
Exactly as planned!
Though her school life
may appear perfect,
Koshi Torako keeps a secret
she mustn't speak to anyone.
She is a former delinquent!
The Vicious Beast of Hino, Tokyo! That's me!
My dark days as a delinquent
too obsessed with shounen manga!
If my secret got out,
all that work making a clean break with high school
and becoming an honor student...
...would go down the drain!
Anyway, my disguise is flawless.
No one will ever see through it!
Or so she thought...
Until this very day.
Wait, the first episode starts
with someone hanging themselves?!
Thank god this is a late-night anime!
This is definitely not good, though!
P-Police? Doctor?
Conan-kun! Wait, no...
Hajime-chan!
Huh? She's alive?
What's going on?
If this isn't a suicide,
why is she hanging there?
Are those antlers?
Ah, they're those things they sell at Toky—
I mean, Chiba Mouseyland...
Wait! Shouldn't they have
come off and let her fall?!
Does this mean
they're real antlers?!
And they're probably deer antlers...
What kind of deer even are you?!
But come to think of it,
aren't male deer the ones with antlers?
Male
Female
UMA
Deergirl
Is she some kind of new UMA, then?
Or maybe a mutant
from some evil organization?!
Paranormal
Deergirl
Either way, that's a lot of snot...
It is twelve degrees Celsius.
Gah! That's disgusting!
And while I was lost in thought,
a bunch of animals showed up to dine on her corpse!
Huh? Want summa this?
You want a piece of me, huh?! Ora Ora Ora!
Want some?! Ora Ora Ora!
Why is she trying to pick a fight
in her situation?
Should I try to help?
She's staring a hole through my head!
So intense!
If I get caught up in all this,
I'll be late for school!
An honor student like me
absolutely cannot be late!
I'll just... pretend I didn't see her...
...and hurry to school...
You're leaving me...
You're really gonna
abandon me like this.
I-I-I-I would never!
I was just about to...
Actually, this is your fault
for hanging there, right?
I'm in a hurry.
I don't have time for playing games...
Tomorrow's news will say,
"Hino City high schooler caught on electric cables dies."
Every morning,
when you walk through this street,
you'll see my face.
"If only I had helped her when I could"...
You'll spend the rest of your life haunted by regret.
All right, already! I get it!
I live!
She's freakin' heavy!
How the—
Would you be so kind as to tell me
how you ended up there?
I woke up this morning and was just,
like, there, y'know? Somehow.
Seriously! Tell me!
However it happened, thank you so much
for helping me, Miss Delinquent!
Oh, I didn't do anything special—
Miss Delinquent?
Huh?! Who're you callin' a delinquent?!
You, miss!
Wh-What are you talking about?!
Me? One as beautiful
and elegant as a peony?
A delinquent?! Th-That's absurd!
That so? Hmm...
But I smell it all over you...
Smell what?
And my antlers are reacting to you.
Wait, what kind of sensors are those?!
Being near her is way too risky...
A-Are you sure you aren't imagining things?
Perhaps you're mistaken...
Oh, I have to get going!
Try not to get caught up there again, okay?
That was close...
My disguise should have been flawless...
How did she...?
What was with that girl?
Everyone, take your seats!
Today, we have a new transfer student
I would like you to meet.
A transfer student?
I got a bad feeling about this...
Come on in!
Coming!
I knew it!
Oh? Huh?
H-How are you stuck again?
Learn your lesson, already!
Nyun!
You're kidding me, right?!
Now, Shikanoko-san,
introduce yourself.
Shikanoko Noko
Lersant! I'm Shikanoko Noko!
You can call me Noko-tan!
Noko-tan!
What a funny girl.
She's a deer!
Why is she getting a normal welcome?
Am I the weirdo here?
And you can sit...
Oh, there's a free seat
next to Koshi-san!
A common trope in school anime:
the conveniently free seat.
This is bad!
If she says anything weird,
my high school life is over!
I have to get ahead of this!
G-Good morning!
Oh, it's you!
So you're a transfer student, huh?
I'm Koshi Torako.
If you have any questions,
don't hesitate to ask!
Thanks!
Huh? Is this actually
gonna work out somehow?
Guess I had nothing to
worry about after all!
You can call me whatever you like.
Whatever I like?
I was just overthinking things...
Got it!
Miss Delinquent!
Miss Delinquent! Miss Delinquent!
I hope we'll get along,
Miss Delinquent!
Koshi-san is a delinquent?!
Her of all people?!
We misheard that, right?!
Hey!
None of you batted an eye at the deer transfer student!
How does this surprise you?!
A d-d-delinquent? Me?
What are you talking about?
Could you please not make things up?
My animal instincts tell me
you're a delinquent.
Are you a wild beast?!
Furthermore...
You're a virgin, aren't you?
Huh?
Huh?!
I mean, my antlers are reacting to you!
What kind of system
do you have going there?!
So Koshi-san's a virgin?
I knew she had to be!
Really?!
Stay out of this, peanut gallery!
Wh-What kind of proof
do you have to claim I'm a virgin...?
Huh? So you're not a virgin?
Well, that's... uh...
Virginity confirmed!
VIRGIN
Toudai-ji,
Nara Park
Koufuku-ji,
It's Koshi-san!
As beautiful as always!
My disgraceful past
nearly got exposed back there...
I have to keep this up...
But I can't let my guard down!
I need to make sure that deer
doesn't expose me as a former delinquent!
Which is why...
...I have to get ahead of her
before she says more weird—
Huh?
A giant pile of sweets on my desk?
Huh?!
Wait, no! That cross-shaped wrapping...
Those are deer crackers!
Deer crackers.
Known as soul food
for the people of Nara prefecture.
(Addendum: So says one theory.)
Students on school trips
commonly try them for laughs...
...but much like their taste,
these jokes are dry and bland.
The only one who would do this is...
It must have been her!
Wait, is she drooling?
What is she, a merlion?
Umm, Shikanoko-san?
What's all of this about?
Nyun? Recompense?
Your face tells a different story!
Miss!
You saved me this morning,
didn't you?
It's my thanks.
Hmm? Oh, that was nothing.
No need to thank me...
What? Deer crackers
not good enough for you?
That's not the issue...
And why do you sound
so cocky all of a sudden?
You want one of my antlers
as a special gift?
They come off?!
Here.
I don't want it!
By the way, they're edible.
Wh-What do they taste like?
Not that I'll try one...
They're tasteless, odorless, and super tough!
You're saying I'd have to force it down?!
If you must insist...
Just this once.
I told you, I don't want it!
And, like, not that I should argue,
but aren't you abandoning your identity too quickly?!
Without antlers,
you're just an ordinary high school girl!
You saved my life...
I'll forsake my entire character for you!
That's too serious!
It's too early to break character!
This is still the first episode,
you know.
Don't want deer crackers...
Don't want antlers...
They reattach...
Ah! Then what you really want...
...is my tender deer flesh?!
Venison
Why are you so wrapped up
with this deer thing?
I get it now!
Go ahead and eat me!
I'm not gonna eat you!
And who are these people?!
I mean, I don't have
anything else to give you!
Look! As you can see,
I have no money.
But you had more deer crackers?
Please, don't make me
give up more...
Why are you acting
like I'm extorting you or something?
And for crackers of all things!
Oops! I let my real side slip!
Hey, Noko-tan!
Do you and Koshi-san know each other?
You've been acting like good friends all day!
Huh?! Wait, Noko-tan?
My nickname. Cute, isn't it?
She's so annoying...
You see, I got stuck on a power line
this morning, and Miss Delinq—
Shikanoko-san! I just remembered,
our teacher wants to see you!
No running in school hallways
Oh my, Koshi-tan...
Why did you bring me here all of a sudden?
Out of order
- The student council
How bold...
What are you imagining?!
Huh? Real question is,
what were you imagining, Koshi-tan?
Huh?!
W-Well, I mean... I-I wasn't...
Koshi-tan...
Bona fide virgin.
Will you shut up?!
And why do you keep calling me Koshi-tan?
It's a nickname.
Doesn't "Noko-tan and Koshi-tan" sound nice?
What are we, a comedy duo?!
Besides, who said you could nickname me?
Okay, Miss Delinq—
Koshi-tan's fine.
She's accepted it.
I mean, it doesn't really matter, anyway.
Can you promise me that you'll never,
ever reveal my true identity?
Nyun?
I'm passing as an honor student here,
so it will be a big problem if anyone finds out.
If you speak a word of this...
There's gonna be hell to pay.
Understand?
Your real identity...
You mean that you're actually a virgin?
You're wro—Well, not wrong,
but that's not what I meant!
Dammit...
You just won't stop calling me out...
Stupid brat!
Stick to the antler gags, will ya?!
Of course...
These antlers are weird, aren't they?
Indoors
O-Oh... I...
I mean, of course a girl who
grows antlers is creepy, right?
Like, what even is a deer anyway
when you really think about it?
I'm sorry if I touched a nerve!
I see... She's probably always
getting laughed at because of her appearance,
and yet I...
I'm a failure of a honor student!
No... A failure of a human being!
I-I'm sorry!
I don't mind the antlers at all!
So? This is better, huh?
What...?
Koshi-tan wanted to know where
the antlers began, but she feared the answer.
Today's been exhausting...
I need to hurry home and prep
for tomorrow's classes...
What was that noise?
Was it from over there?
Excuse me! Is anyone there?
I just heard a loud noise.
Is everything oka—
Deer
P-Police? Doctor?
Conan-kun... Wait, no. Hajime-chan!
Nyun, Koshi-tan!
Sh-Sh-Shikanoko-san, is that b-b-blood?
Did something happen?
Oh, my bad!
I fell off the stepladder
and scraped my knee!
No, your head!
Your freakin' head!
What a cute bandage!
Shut up! What are you doing
in this unused warehouse, anyway?
I was cleaning!
Cleaning? By yourself?
Yep! Thanks, Koshi-tan!
All right, back to work!
Nyun?
Okay, okay. I'll help you.
What? For real?
W-Well, you're hurt,
and who knows what you'll do
if I leave you alone...
Yippee! Thanks!
She is undeniably a tsundere.
Cleaning is is a lot of work,
but you look like you're having fun, huh?
Well, yeah.
I'm doing it with you, Koshi-tan.
Y-You're too much!
We're just cleaning!
I guess even cleaning can be fun
if you do it with others!
Oh my, it looks so much cleaner already!
Ms. Ukai?
Ms. Ukai, lersant!
Hey there! Lersant!
So you've been helping out, Koshi-san?
Thank you! It must have been difficult.
Oh, not at all! It was nothing!
I feel much better knowing you'll be
joining the Deer Club too, Koshi-san!
Of cour—
Excuse me? Deer Club?
Well, as promised,
you can use this space however you like.
Hooray!
Wait, what the heck is a Deer Club?
And why am I joining?!
What? You don't know?
I founded the Deer Club!
What is this avant-garde sounding club?!
I promised that if she cleaned up in here,
she could use it as a clubroom.
Right?
Don't give me that "Right?" crap!
This won't end well for me
if I get sucked into this pointless club!
Oh, it's such a relief!
You're so reliable
and compassionate, Koshi-san.
Like an older sister!
With how cheerful and kind you are,
I'm sure this will be an enjoyable club!
It'll be like home for us!
You're so smart too,
so maybe you'll even win an award!
Maybe even make it to nationals!
If you join, I'm sure the Deer Club
will do incredible things!
You can count on me!
Koshi-tan was easily persuaded.
Okay, Shikanoko-san,
make sure you fill out the club approval form.
Nyun!
Club name: Deer Club.
Club president: Koshi Torako.
Activities: Taking care of deer, mostly.
Wait a minute!
Why am I the club president?
Because you're the president, Koshi-tan.
Because you're the president, Koshi-san.
Huh? Am I the weirdo here?
Isn't this the Deer Club?
If Shikanoko-san, a literal deer,
can't be president, then who can?
Oh, that's what you meant?
Look, it says here that the deer club's activities are
"taking care of deer, mostly", right?
Huh? Yeah...
Club member
I'll be the Deer Club's
resident deer, you see...
The Deer Club's resident deer?!
Deer
The president is responsible for her care!
That's you, Koshi-tan!
I am not okay with this!
What kind of club takes care of deer, anyway?
Is this an agricultural school?!
Here, submitted.
And accepted!
Whoa! You work too fast!
Well, then, madam president,
I'm counting on you to look after Shikanoko-san.
Take good care of me, nyun!
All right...
Because she said "leave it to me"
with such a wide smile,
Koshi-tan found herself unable to argue.
Deer Club - New members wanted!
The Deer Club's inaugurated! Hooray!
What an unexpected turn of events
for just one day...
I'll bring more deer crackers tomorrow!
Oh well.
Now, then, can you start by
giving me a good brushing?
You can't be serious!
And what's with
that scrub brush thingy?
It's for animals.
Fine, guess I have no choice!
Lersant!
Dammit, why me of all people?
Ugh, you're going to make me do this
every club meeting, aren't you?
Curse you, foul beast!
S-So scary!
I don't know what's going on,
but the Deer Club's battle
has only just begun!
A bustling crowd of gathering deer
Where did they even come from, all these deer
Deer, deer, deer are all that's here!
Do those deer crackers really taste so great?
Round and golden brown, don't tease me with them...
Why ever would you really want them that bad?
Deer, deer, deer!
Are there smarts inside all those deer?
How come they always know if we have them?
Deer, deer, deer are all that's here!
Come rain, come sun, it's all for the deer
Subtitles: DeerGod
Alternative subtitles are available
Switch to English (United States) to view them
This is a work of fiction. All the characters, places, and businesses shown are fictitious. Any resemblance to reality is purely coincidental.
I made it!
Deer!
Deer, deer, deer!
Deer?
Nyun
Shikanoko the careless doe has Koshi on her toes
Shikanoko the careless doe has Koshi on her toes (nyun nyun)
Doe eyes popping up here and there without a care
Antlers jamming out, and the body of a girl?!
It's the craze that's in the latest rumors
Let's see what you can do, greenhorn!
"They've been found in Japan since ancient times."
Deer crackers? I'll take a lifetime supply!
Reindeer are comrades, wild goats are bovines
but together, we're all even-toed ungulates!
Gracefully dancing the nyun step...
'Til the break of dawn!
One, two, three!
Even with a life of ruminating, nyunyunyun
you can never predict deer-tinted days!
Avant-garde is perfect, the chaos will only deepen!
You'll get hooked before you know it, nyunyunyun
on the chaos & nonsense of deer-tinted days!
Bring on the unprecedented!
Anything goes, there's no rules here
Your smile always fills me with energy
Are you my match, m-m-my deerest?!
While there's times you keep me on my toes,
I want to be with you forever!
Shikanoko the careless doe has Koshi on her toes!
DEER MEETS DARKNESS GIRL
Let's reacquaint ourselves.
This girl's name is Koshi Torako.
Secretly a former delinquent.
Burying away her past upon entering high school,
she established herself as an honor student,
and is now president of the student council,
as well as class rep. However...
A transfer deer (?) named
Shikanoko Noko saw through her disguise...
...and exposed her virginity.
Totally unrelatedly,
she was too easily persuaded...
...and was duped into becoming
the president of the mysterious Deer Club.
Now, once again,
we find her reluctantly going back...
All right! Time for Deer Club!
Perhaps not so reluctantly?
Well, it's not as if I'm
looking forward to going back...
Huh? So which is it?
I did a teensy-weensy bit of redecorating
for the club room this morning...
...and it turned out gorgeous!
But that doesn't mean I'm, like,
that excited for club time today...
...'cause I'm definitely not!
You don't say?
Besides, it's the president's job
to make the club room comfortable.
I can't wait to see her reaction!
Koshi-tan, you're amazing!
I had you all wrong!
Naturally!
All that's left is the wallpaper...
Oh! Maybe I'll get some shelves, too!
So much left to do!
Wait for me, my utopia!
THE DEER WILL PAY
Utopia is canceled until further notice.
Kumagorou!
Wh-What happened here?
Where's my utopia?
The utopia I poured my life savings and four hours
of back-breaking work into this morning...!
She woke up at 3:00 AM.
Koshi-tan, you okay?
It's dangerous over there.
Come here.
Was this you?!
Is this your doing?!
Did you ruin my utopia?!
Nyun? Whatcha talkin' 'bout?
It was already jacked up
when I got here.
Besides, it's not safe.
What do you mean?
Someone's out to kill me today.
Who? And why?
No idea.
But it's probably whoever
trashed our room.
On my way to school,
I fell down a five-meter-deep pitfall,
was pelted with spears
raining from the sky,
and even encountered
plastic bottles filled with water.
How are you even alive?!
Didn't you get speared in the head?!
And hold up, water bottles?
Even cats aren't scared of those anymore!
My antlers got totally
caught in the door, too!
You broke it again?!
Forget that!
I'm telling you, it's not safe here!
Get a grip.
Think about it.
There's no way anyone's after you.
You sure?
Of course.
Let's just step outside,
get some fresh air and think calmly—
Yo. You really gonna
blow cover like that?
This is a battlefield!
Who are you?!
Didn't I teach you being careless
is life or death out here?
You didn't teach me squat!
I was born in the peaceful Heisei era!
But hold on,
is someone seriously after you?
Seems so.
Tch. Screw this noise! I'm out!
What?! You'd abandon
your teacher and turn tail?!
Knock it off!
Since when am I your student?
I'm so over getting caught up
in this dumb cra—
Koshi-tan,
you all right in the head?
That wasn't an insult.
Who the hell are you?
Give me back my utopia!
Now she's mad!
You're going down!
I don't care if you're a soldier
or an assassin...
Bring it!
Crap! A grenade!
Huh?
Deer crackers?!
Hey! It's a trap!
You dimwitted dope!
Wait, wait, wait!
What is it, Koshi-tan?!
Open your eyes! It's a trap!
The trap to end all traps!
What kind of dummy
runs drooling right into a trap?
A trap...
Shikanoko?
Long, long ago, a deer was once asked...
"Why do deer eat deer crackers?"
Their answer?
"Because the deer crackers are there!"
Shikanoko!
I'm sorry, Koshi-tan...
But I love deer crackers
more than anything else in this world!
Yahoo!
Ah.
I goofed up.
I told you it was a tra—
I lost a little steam at the end there
and didn't reach the deer crackers!
You meant that?!
Hey! You over there
who has it out for me!
I know you can hear me!
My name is Noko-tan!
Reveal yourself!
I accept this battle fair and square!
Haven't you lost already?
The defeated deer
doth protest too much.
Oh, and bring me
more deer crackers, please!
Are you in any position
to be asking that?
You're awfully bold for roadkill.
Huh?
I had planned to be
rid of you sooner,
but I made some
unfortunate miscalculations.
I'll gladly do battle.
It will be a quick trip to hell for you.
This girl...
I've survived countless war zones,
but she easily captured me.
She's no amateur.
Who the hell are you?!
Anko?
What the heck are you doing here?
Sis!
I so missed you!
You missed me?
I would have seen you when I got home...
I wanna be with you every second, every minute,
24 hours a day, 365 days a year!
I can't get enough of your smell!
Can you, like, not?
And wait a sec,
why aren't you at school?
You're so cute when you're mad!
I wuv you!
Did you hear a word I said?
Koshi-tan, who's this?
Oh, my bad.
This is Koshi Anko.
My younger sister.
Koshi... Anko...
Like... smooth bean paste!
You must be picturing
something tasty, huh?
You're in for it now!
Never stare at me that way, pest!
Nyun?
Shikanoko Noko.
I'll never forgive you.
What's your issue with her?
Wait, was this all you?
Yes. I did it.
Why would you...?
It's all that deer's fault! All of it!
She's changed you!
You used to run home
straight for me after school!
To you? You mean where our family lives?
You've been coming home
so late recently...
I'm always home by seven!
I decided to follow you since
I wondered why you were out so late,
and found you cavorting with a deer
in some weirdo private club?! How obscene!
The only obscene thing here
is your reasoning!
Then you left so early
this morning to top it off...
You're only thinking about
your little deer love nest!
That comfy couch? Those adorable rugs?!
What are they doing in a club room?
Obscene! What were you two
planning on doing in there?!
W-Well...
She wanted to object,
but couldn't admit she had selfish motives.
You can't answer? Does that mean...
You slept together?
Of course not!
Are you psychotic?!
And what's with the kunai?!
Are you Iga? Kouga? Hokage?!
Hey, help me out here!
Koshi-tan is my woman!
Not helping!
Why are you running with it?
That's not what's happening here!
You'll never get Koshi-tan
no matter what kind of bean paste you are!
Now you've done it, dummy!
I knew it!
You stole my sister's virginity, didn't you?!
See?! I knew this would happen!
Do you realize how hard I've been
protecting my sister's virginity?!
I don't remember asking you for that!
This can't be forgiven...
The deer for taking my sister from me...
And my sister for
crossing a line with a deer.
I haven't crossed any lines!
Not even the Chuuou Main Line!
Setting: Hino City
I belong at your side...
Anyone who stands in my way
is my enemy...
So it's settled...
I'll destroy it all.
Anko...
I thought that if I ruined
this weirdo Deer Club of yours...
...and exterminated that pest,
my sister would return home to me.
But I've changed my mind.
Nyun.
You said something about
a fair and square battle, right?
Sounds fun.
I'll do battle with you.
But if I win,
you'll spend the rest of your life
as a deer at Nara Park.
Nara?
Of course, if I lose, I'll accept your
degenerate relationship with my sister...
...and graciously leave you alone.
Quit giving people the wrong idea!
Anko, get a hold of yourself.
This is ridiculous.
There's no reason to fight.
Why? It was the deer's idea.
Well, I guess that's true...
Fine. Let's battle.
Wait, are you serious?
If you become a Nara Park deer,
what will happen to the club?
Don't worry, Koshi-tan!
Huh?
Believe in me!
The Deer Club's bonds
go harder than deer crackers!
Shikanoko...
What the heck are you talking about?!
Deer crackers aren't hard!
They're thin and crispy!
But I have one condition, too!
What?
If I win the battle...
Please give me loads of deer crackers!
Just go to Nara already!
The Deer Club faces its first major crisis!
What will happen to the club? To Noko-tan?
The duel to decide the fate of
the Deer Club and deer crackers now begins!
I'll deport you to Nara Park like that!
All the deer crackers I can eat...
Can I leave now?
Big Shrine Gate,
Miyajima
Itsukushima Shrine,
1st Hinominami High School
Chitty Chitty King of Koshi Torako Competition!!
The first-ever Hinominami High School
Chitty Chitty King of Koshi Torako Showdown!
Let's introduce our two contestants!
What is going on here?!
Koshi Torako's younger sister
with an intense sister complex,
Koshi Anko-chan!
Does anything else in the world
matter besides my sister and I?
Hey, what's the deal here?!
The Deer Club's resident deer,
Shikanoko Noko-san!
I'll do whatever it takes
for those deer crackers!
Is anyone listening to me?!
How does it feel having these two
fight over you, Koshi-san?
I... I don't know what's happening...
You sound awfully excited!
Did you hear a word of what I said?!
And today's grand prizes are...
For Anko-chan, the right to deport
Noko-tan to Nara Park!
Deportation
Rights
And for Noko-tan,
a one hundred year supply of deer crackers!
Where'd those even come from?!
And I'm your host,
the advisor of the Deer Club, Ukai!
Do teachers have nothing better to do?
All right! Let's get started!
You put way too much effort
into this set...
Question one!
What does Koshi-san do every—
"What does Koshi-san
do every night before bed?"
Answer: She talks to the plushies in her room
and gives them each a goodnight kiss.
Correct!
Stop! What kind of question is that?!
Why are you violating my privacy?!
Is that wrong?
Of course it is!
But it's making your fans
go even crazier for you!
Koshi-san likes plushies?
Adorable!
Fan for life!
That's not the issue here!
Here's a picture to prove it!
My privacy! My privacy!
Please stop asking these questions!
Onto the second question!
You're ignoring me?!
Is Koshi-san currently—
Tch!
Noko-tan was quicker this time!
Your answer, please!
"Is Koshi-tan currently
not wearing a bra?"
The answer: She's wearing a bra top,
which isn't a real bra.
Again, what are these questions?!
Correct!
Y-You can't prove that without looking!
Schrödinger's bra.
Well then,
let's have a look at the footage!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Seriously!
Why do you have this footage?!
Question three!
Can I please leave now?!
Koshi-san has da—
"She has dated how many
boys or girls in total?"
Answer: Zero!
Uh, there could be someone,
you don't know that!
Not a soul.
Sorry! Incorrect!
Nyun?!
Koshi-san has dated
exactly zero boys or girls in total,
but why is that the case?
Please answer in twenty words or less.
Do you really need to dig that deep?!
Okay, Anko-chan!
Let's hear your answer!
Despite her peers forming relationships,
high school has been loveless...
...due to her shoujo manga mentality
of "awaiting true love".
Precisely twenty words.
Correct!
Quit analyzing me!
Her favorite manga magazine
is Bessatsu Friend.
Question four!
What incident from Koshi-san's
childhood has she been keeping secret?
She wet the bed until she was ten.
Correct!
Don't say that!
What thing does Koshi-san
surprisingly like?
Children's anime.
Correct!
Why is that surprising? Who cares?
Question five! What is Koshi-san's—
Egg on rice!
Correct!
How were you even able to answer that?!
Unbelievable!
The contestants are locked in a tie!
How much longer
will they violate my privacy?
This can't be right!
Why does this freaky deer
know so much about my sister?
There must be something more to this!
I know!
She's connected to the nationwide deer network,
Shika Shika Network (SSN)!
It's collecting my sister's data,
sending it to the supercomputer Shikagaku,
which then analyzes
and transmits it to her antlers!
It's about time I resorted to violence!
You let your guard down!
I had plenty more traps left!
So what was even the point of the quiz?
Koshi-tan's privacy was violated for nothing.
I'll riddle you with holes
before deporting you to Nara Park!
You can dodge them?!
What is up with this deer?
Take a hit already!
Take this! And this! And this!
I'm exhausted.
Why don't I just use this
as a smokescreen and bail?
You vermin!
Sis!
Shikanoko!
Hey, Shikanoko!
Koshi-tan... I feel... so sleepy...
What are you saying?!
Don't leave me, Shikanoko!
Open your eyes, Shikanoko! Shikanoko!
How could you...?
You follow me around, make me join your club...
Got me into this mess...
And now this...
Don't you dare go and
leave me all alone!
Lersant!
Nyun...
Shikanoko, you're alive!
I-I'm glad you're not dead, but how?
Earlier...
Nyun.
The crackers I picked up musta saved me.
Are we in some old-timey movie?!
Deer crackers aren't even hard,
they're thin and crispy!
Shikanoko...
Thanks for saving my sister.
I admit defeat.
I was so foolishly blinded
by hate and anger,
I almost hurt my own sister...
I'm a failure as a little sister!
You're the one
who should be by her si—
That's not true!
It's not true!
Because of you, miss— No...
Koshian, because of you, I was able to save Koshi-tan
with the deer crackers you gave me.
You saved her life!
We could be good friends,
don'tcha think?
May I call you... Noko-tan?
Huh?
Of course!
Huh...?
Take care of my sister
from here on out, okay, Noko-tan?
Leave it to me, Koshian!
Noko-tan! Koshian!
They're so lovely!
In the end, Koshi-tan couldn't process a single thing
that happened when all was said and done.
At least...
Starting tomorrow,
I'm wearing a bra every day.
The next day
It's white today.
You have x-ray vision?!
A bustling crowd of gathering deer
Where did they even come from, all these deer
Deer, deer, deer are all that's here!
Do those deer crackers really taste so great?
Round and golden brown, don't tease me with them...
Why ever would you really want them that bad?
Deer, deer, deer!
Are there smarts inside all those deer?
How come they always know if we have them?
Deer, deer, deer are all that's here!
Come rain, come sun, it's all for the deer
Subtitles: DeerStalker
Alternative subtitles are available
Switch to English (United States) to view them
Oh, shoot!
This is a work of fiction. All characters, places, and businesses shown are fictitious. Any resemblance to reality is purely coincidental.
I got sidetracked and ended up running late!
Deer Club
Sorry for the wait!
Cam 1
Cam 2
Cam 3
Cam 4
A-A deer!
shikanoko nokonoko koshitantan
Shikanoko's doe-eyed nonchalance, Koshi-tan's tale of vigilance
shikanoko tokotoko arawaru nokonoko
Little deer's here and there without a care
tsunotsuno pyokopyoko mitame wa onnya no ko
Antlers jutting out of her hair, though she's a girl all too fair?!
chikagoro uwasa no nakanaka kiwamono
She's become quite the affair
otenami ikahodo hena choko
Let's see what you've got, ya little square!
sugoku mukashi kara Japan ni seisoku
Been in Japan since the olden days
shika senbei nara mugen ni kudasai
If you've got deer crackers, I'll take a million!
tonakai wa nakama kamoshika wa ushika
Reindeer are just fine, goats may be bovine...
demo demo matomete guuteimoku
But hey, we've all got our hooves!
nun no step de odorou
Let us dance the nyun step...
'till the crack of dawn!
yo ga akeru made
One, two, three!
nando datte hansuu shite nununun
Try as you might, nyunyunyun
yosoku fukanou shikairo days
you'll never predict our fawn-filled days!
Avant-garde's darn right, only more chaos to be had!
avant-garde de all right chaos mashi mashi
itsu no ma ni kuse ni natte nununun
You'll soon be right at home, nyunyunyun
hacha de mecha na shikairo days
with our chaotic, fawn-filled days!
hatenkou bacchi come on
Delusional lunacy, come on!
nandemo ari rule nante nashi
Anything goes, no rules here, comrade!
kimi no egao de genki mantan
Your smile brightens my day in one glance
moshikashite unmei no ma ma my deer
Could this be fate, m-m-my deer?!
kokoro no dokoka de koshitantan
I swear by my inner vigilance
kimi to nara itsu ma demo
I'll always be with you!
shikanoko nokonoko koshitantan
Shikanoko's doe-eyed nonchalance, Koshi-tan's tale of vigilance!
Enter Bashame
W-W-Why is there a deer here?!
Well, I suppose for the Deer
Club, it isn't that strange...
Deer Club
If anything, seeing them around
has become completely ordinary.
How did I not notice until now?
Deer
Crackers
Either way, don't eat our deer
crackers like you own the place!
Hey, Shikanoko!
This a friend of yours?
Where is she?
Wait! Could it be...?!
Shikanoko!
What are you trying to pull?!
I already know it's you, Shikanoko!
Take that thing off already!
She's not listening?
That girl thinks she can mess with me, huh?
She's got guts. I'll give her that.
I'm tearing that ridiculous
disguise of hers right off!
Take it off! Take that stupid costume off!
Did you seriously think I wouldn't catch on?!
Deer Club
Boy, I sure am parched...!
It's such a long ways from
the school building to here!
Oh, right! I bought something real nice earlier!
Ta-da!
Two XL servings of our school's
Limited Edition Springtime
Sakuramochi-flavored Tapioca Milk Tea!
It's too bad a regular old deer can't have any!
You poor thing!
And here I had one for you too!
Since you can't drink these,
I guess I have them all to myself!
You cool with that? I'll be having your share!
She doesn't care?!
Damn. Looks like it'll take more
than tapioca to get her to crack.
Manjiro!
Deer are herbivores.
They eat grass and leaves.
My beloved little Manjiro is gonna be deer food!
Koshi-tan fosters every decorative plant in the
club room and lovingly named them all herself.
Iruka
Umako
Emishi
Don't eat him, you stupid deer!
What in the world is that noise?! I've never heard anything like it!
When provoked, male deer first
intimidate by uttering a deep groan.
One should stay clear until they calm down.
Not backing down, huh?
Well, I can't afford to either.
Manjiro and the others' lives are in my hands!
Guess I'll have to use force!
Have a taste of your inane water bottle weakness!
Noko-tan is deathly afraid of water bottles.
How's that? You can't move a muscle!
If you want me to get rid of
them, that disguise has to go!
What?!
T-This girl!
When did she overcome her fear of water bottles?!
If I don't think of something quick,
Manjiro and the others are goners!
Is there anything I can use to distract her? Think!
T-That's it!
S-So that's where my notebook full
of my deepest darkest secrets was!
Secret
I really should torch this
shameful past of mine already!
Glance.
Secret
But come to think of it, Shikanoko
and I are such close friends now!
If she'd only drop her disguise, she might
get a little peek before it's gone forever!
This thing's so embarrassing,
I can't even leave it back home.
I can't believe lugging it around
everywhere is finally going to come in handy!
Still, if I'm gonna sink
this low, I'm sure she'll...
Bingo! Hook, line, and sinker!
Time to seal the deal!
S-She might even get to hear all those ridiculous
songs that I came up with way back when, too!
What, really?! Lemme hear, lemme hear!
Oh, if you insist! Just one, okay?!
One, two, three, four.
Go get 'em, newly reborn Koshi-tan!
I can hear the winds of sadness!
Might someone be weeping away?
Behind the school building at dusk!
The starving tiger's territory!
An untouchable sanctuary!
If you aren't careful, she'll bite your head off!
However, I can't just ignore someone singing
so sorrowfully! I'll wipe those tears right away!
My, my. And here I was trying not to stand out!
Three minutes?
Three seconds is plenty!
Go! Fight! Koshi-tan!
I might be reformed, but I'm
still a force to be reckoned with!
This tiger's fist will smash
your face to smoldering pieces!
A tiger's paw ain't so soft, y'know?
When you're crying, let yourself be heard!
Koshi-tan! Koshi-tan!
I am the reborn Koshi-tan!
Now for the second verse! Let's go!
Go get 'em, newly reborn Koshi-tan!
Woah there! I almost forgot
not to perform more than one.
Huh? That's too bad!
Sorry, no can do!
Until you take that thing off, I won't...
I wanna hear more!
Let's hear another round of
the reborn Koshi-tan's song!
Sh-Shikanoko?
There're two of you? W-Why?!
Two of me? What're you
talking about, Koshi-tan?
I'm talking about that! That!
They can communicate?
He says he came here after
escaping from the Hino Zoo.
E-Escaping?
Maybe the scent of all these
deer crackers led him here.
What the hell?!
By the way, what's with this notebook?
Oh! There's that original song from earlier!
C'mon, keep going!
Go get 'em, newly reborn Koshi-tan!
Koshi-tan's desire to crawl in a hole was so overwhelming,
she decided to skip finding one altogether and dig it herself.
Lersant! Take caribou!
Lersant.
And so, the deer went on its
way back to the Hino Zoo.
Kinkasan
Koganeyama Shrine
Sanrikufukkou
National Park
Entrance
Ceremony​
Under the sun's warm embrace,
cherry blossoms burst into full bloom.
To all of our new students,
congratulations on your first day here!
On behalf of the student body, I'd like
to offer you all a heartfelt welcome.
Spring.
Koshi-tan's class enters its third year.
Seems there're no patented
Sazae-san time warps at play here.
I wish I got to see Koshi-tan's
student council president speech.
I'll bet you were pretty cool up there, huh?
You bet I was.
Woah! Hang on!
Are you okay?!
Why are you here of all places?
What's wrong?! Are you sick?!
Shall I take you to the nurse's office?!
Or do I need to call an ambulance?!
Maybe even the police?!
The JSDF?!
Looks like ol' Bashame here felt a
bit too warm and fell right asleep.
I-Is that so?
Bashame?
I'm just glad you're feeling okay.
But what are you doing here?
You're a new student, aren't you?
Bashame came here to meet you!
Huh?
Ba
Sha
Me
Bashame is Bashame Meme, a first year.
Bashame looks up to you so much,
she just couldn't wait to meet you!
Ukai-sensei told Bashame
you'd be here, so here she is!
So, you were so captivated by the wonderful honor student
at the entrance ceremony that you came to see her?
Bashame wants to be just like you!
So, please, please let Bashame be your disciple!
Sorry, but no can do.
Not that I don't appreciate it...
Shikanoko-senpai!
"Shikanoko-senpai"?
W-What?! Her, and not me?!
Who might you be?
I just gave that entrance speech you heard earlier!
I'm the student council president, dangit!
Bashame wanted to meet Shikanoko-senpai,
so she waited right here!
Is this girl nuts or something?
Bashame-san, why'd you pick this dolt—
Er, Shikanoko-san, to look up to?
Glad you asked!
Before the entrance ceremony started,
I was passed out in front of the school gate.
Why?
My tummy is so grumbly.
Bashame is done for.
The entrance ceremony is
going to start without me.
Bashame will die before she
even makes her high school debut.
Want it?
Thank you very much.
Later, then.
Ah, please wait!
Um, what's your name?!
I haven't done anything worth remembering.
And so, Shikanoko-senpai is the
one who Bashame owes her life to.
A deer cracker saved your life?
After that, Bashame found herself thinking
throughout the whole entrance ceremony...
What an amazing role model.
Bashame wants to be just like her.
Bashame wants to be a deer like her!
You want to be a deer?
That's why Bashame has to become your disciple!
You want to be her disciple...
Why are there even more
butterflies swarming you?!
Lersant.
Hey, what do we do about this girl?
The name was Bashame, was it not?
Yes! Bashame here!
Do you truly have the resolve to become a deer?
What's with that tone?!
What do you mean resolve to become a deer?!
Yes! Bashame will do all
it takes to become a deer!
What kind of class is this?!
I suppose that means you'll have
to enlist in the Deer Club first!
Of course! Bashame will join the Deer Club!
Could you two stop ignoring every word I say?!
The president of the Deer Club
is Koshi-tan, our caretaker.
Thus, you should be asking for
Koshi-tan to look after you, not me.
Yes, ma'am! Understood!
Listen to your caretaker!
Wait, what is this?
Now that I'm out of middle school, I finally
get to attend the same school as Onee-chan!
And with my application to the Deer Club, I'll be able
to spend every waking moment of my life with her!
I can do this and that to her all that I want!
Onee-chan!
Koshi-tan-senpai, please allow
Bashame to bask in your care as well.
Wait! Don't!
Onee-chan?!
Anko?!
What are you doing with another woman?!
Hooray. The Deer Club has
gained two new members.
Kinkasan as
seen from
Gobanshoyama
It took a lot to get there, but
we now have four club members.
The Deer Club has finally become an official club!
Up until now, it didn't feel like
anything more than a way to kill time,
but I feel like we can really
push the envelope now!
All right, you guys!
Starting today, we're gonna go all out!
Shikanoko Noko
3rd Year
Status...
Deer
Matching cups with Onee-chan.
An
Koshi
Koshi Anko
1st Year
Status...
Self-Proclaimed
Onee-chan Caretaker
An
Koshi
Bashame Meme
1st Year
Status...
More Human
Than Deer
Yum!
Koshi Torako
3rd Year
Status...
Club Prez/
Caretaker
I can't let things stay like this!
It's time to fix the Deer Club.
Deer Club
Meeting!
And so, we're having our first
Deer Club Strategy Meeting.
Now there's a start.
You're so cute when you're serious!
Quiet down there!
A new term just started,
yet you lot are loafing around!
Do you hold no respect for the Deer Club at all?!
As for what there is to respect...
Do you really want me to answer that?
I'm so disappointed.
The Deer Club I worked so hard to build....
It's...
If others find out about our indolent club activities...
Our budget'll go down the gutter!
Even my hard-earned position as head
of the student council will crumble away!
Learning that Koshi-tan used to be a
delinquent was already quite the shock,
but knowing that she's this
blunt is downright hilarious!
Yet another of her charms!
Deer Club
Meeting!
We can't keep going like this!
Each of you needs to decide
on a solid goal to work towards!
Okay!
First up, Shikanoko!
Deer Club
Meeting!
As the club's main representative, and
for the sake of your status as senior deer,
set an example for our
kouhai and state your goal!
I suppose so. My goal...
Oh!
I wanna bathe in a tub full of deer crackers!
Absolutely not.
Syunyun. Shot down.
Do you intend to spend our
whole budget on deer crackers?!
Proposal rejected!
Take this seriously!
Another goal of mine, huh...
I got nothing.
Wasn't the Deer Club your idea?!
Why did you even start it?!
This girl's hopeless.
It's like she's trying
to set a bad example!
Deer Club
Meeting!
Next up, deer apprentice Bashame!
Don't cook rice in the club room!
Koshi-tan-senpai, want some?
I don't!
You're the one who said she
wanted to become a deer!
Surely you have some sort of goal in mind!
I guess so.
Bashame wants to make her own rice paddy!
Wuzzat?
A-A rice paddy?
I'd take any field, really.
No. I still don't follow.
Bashame realized something.
Us deer need to scrape by in the
harsh savannah that is modern society,
and the key to that is self-sufficiency!
As such, we'll start by erecting
a rice field next to the club room!
Bashame will cultivate her rice
just as any proud deer would!
What do you think a deer is?!
Let's look forward to autumn.
Deer Club
Meeting!
I swear, it's nothing but nonsense with you all.
It's all up to you, Anko!
You're the only one I can trust here!
Let's see.
I joined the Deer Club so that I could help you, so...
Staying by your side and supporting
you in any way I can, I suppose?
Anko...! That's my little sister!
You really are the only one I can rely on!
If I can manage it, I'd love to make it so
you can't possibly live without me either!
Yikes! Give me back that praise
I showered you with three seconds ago!
Deer Club
Meeting!
What's your goal then, Koshi-tan?
Unlike you all, I've thought this through!
What is it?
I've got plenty of goals, but the first one is...
The first one?
I want to make the club room cuter!
I think you've done enough there...
No, this building used to be
an old storehouse, you see.
I'd like to rebuild it cuter than ever.
Doesn't Koshi-tan's goal have the
absolute least to do with the Deer Club?
Is it okay for the student council head
to have such a conflict of interest?
Seems like a pitch we should shelve.
I-Is it really that bad for
the club room to look nice?!
Plus, isn't it my responsibility to make sure that
the deer passing through have a nice environment?!
If that's the case, you should let
me have my deer cracker bath!
And Bashame's rice paddy!
And let me live out my fantasies of doing
this and that with you in the club room!
How come Anko's the only one who shifted gears?!
Frankly, you're the one who's in the wrong here!
The purpose of the Deer Club
is to take care of deer in need!
As the caretaker, you need
to consider my needs more!
If you're gonna be like this, I'm just gonna leave!
What?!
That'd take the "deer" right out
of the Deer Club, wouldn't it?
And then we'd just be another disbanded club.
Huh?
When they come knocking asking who's to blame,
we'd only be able to say it was her, wouldn't we?
Hey!
Before we discuss strategy or whatever, we need
to talk about the working conditions of the deer!
TREASURE
YOUR DEER!
Well, you do have one hell of a point...
Damn it.
Then, what do you want me to do?
TREASURE
YOUR DEER!
Brush me.
Well, that's reasonable.
TREASURE
YOUR DEER!
Here.
TREASURE
YOUR DEER!
Now, show me what you've got!
I see!
If you want to become a better deer,
a proper brushing is priority number one!
Bashame hears you loud and clear!
That's our Noko-tan-senpai!
No. I don't think she's trying
to teach you anything here.
Koshi-tan-senpai!
Bashame's hair is right here!
What?
Senpai, I don't care a lick about you,
but if you're saying you're gonna go the mile and
brush Bashame's hair, I'll take you right up on that!
Where'd all that sass come from?!
And I said nothing of the sort!
You two, or rather, you little does...
You don't know a thing about the Onee-chan of
mine who's taking such good care of you, do you?
The two of us have been practically married for 15 years.
I'm a far better fit for her than either of you greenhorns.
That's right. To be frank...
If there's anyone who should be
the Deer Club's resident deer, it's me!
When did you become a deer?!
What happened to the whole supporting me thing?!
So, Onee-chan, what say you?
You want to brush me far more
than those pests, don't you?
Don't you?
The pressure...!
We'll just have to hold a contest to
see who's the most fit to be our deer!
I'll gladly take you all on!
Bashame won't stand down!
This was supposed to be a meeting!
I'm the deer!
It's me!
Deer!
So this is the ever-troublesome Deer Club, huh?
warawara atsumaru shika
Hustling-bustling, all together, de-er!
dokokara kuru no ka shika
Where'd they come from, all these many de-er!
shika shika shika shika inai
Deer, deer, deer are all that's here!
sonna ni oishii shika senbei
Are those deer crackers really that great?
They're all too round and golden brown...
marukute kongari
jirasanaide
Don't tempt me, oh please!
doushite sonna ni hoshigaru no
Why, oh why, would one want them oh so badly?
shika shika shika
Deer, deer, deer!
atama ga ii no ka shika
Might they be geniuses, those deer?
How do they always know who has 'em?
motteru to bareru no naze
shika shika shika shika inai
Deer, deer, deer are all that's here!
harete mo ame demo shika no tame
Be it blazing, or even raining, we're here for the deer!