What's wrong with not letting my sound die down?
nariyamanakute nani ga warui
What's wrong with being young?
seishun de nani ga warui
Hey, why doesn't it stop?
nee doushite tomaranai
The rhythm that I can't stop
tomerannai rizumu ga
keeps reverberating through my body
karada no naka hibiiteiru
The melody playing in my earphones
iyafon kara nagareru merodi dake ga
is the only thing that lets me be who I am
boku wo boku de isasete kureta
The sky is tinged in red
akairo ni somaru sora
But what color is my soul?
boku no kokoro wa naniiro nan darou
Tell me
oshiete
where should I go?
boku wa doko e mukaeba ii?
I've always been searching
zutto sagashiteita
for something precious
taisetsu na nanika wo
Hey!
hora!
If everything's going to be lost some day
itsuka nakushite shimau mono bakari nara
let's engrave it as deep as we can
tsuyoku kizande okou
Now!
ima!
My most pathetic nights and cackling laughter
mijime na yoru mo baka warai mo
And days when I couldn't say more than "You know..."
ano ne, sono ato ga ienakatta hi mo
I'm alive now, yeah Springtime of life
aimu araibu nau ie supuringu taimu obu raifu
What's wrong with not letting my sound die down?
nariyamanakute nani ga warui
What's wrong with being young?
seishun de nani ga warui
Subtitle source: neoHEVC
https://nyaa.si/view/1678808