The tune that plays when my loneliness
fumitsukerareta kodoku
and the pedal are stepped on
to pedaru kara
Tracks down my cheeks over and over again
nandomo narihibiku neiro ga hoho ni tsutau
The pounding of my loneliness
uchitsukerareta kodoku ni
Is joined by the rhythm of the snare drum
sunea no rizumu ga kasanatte
To create a solid pulse
tashika na kodou ni naru
Someone, please remove the distortion on my heart
dareka kokoro no noizu wo totte
And take a look inside me
watashi wo nozoite yo
Nobody can get inside my heart
daremo kokoro no oku ni wa irenai
But it's the kind of night
keredo kitai shiteshimau
when I hope someone will
sonna yoru
Distortion, it's motion
Once it starts, there's no stopping it
hajimattara mou tomaranai
Limits can be overwritten with experience
seigen mo keiken de nurikaerareru sa
Isn't that right?
sou darou
Distortion is always like that
disutooshon itsumo sou
My heart takes off, outpacing my left brain
sanou oikoshite kokoro ga hashiridasu
Toward where you are
kimi no
An escort to the next note
tsugi no oto ni esukooto
Distortion on my day-to-day anguish
hibi no urei ni disutooshon
The chord I play when I'm alone at night
hitori no yoru narasu koodo
Is it the same for you?
kimi mo onaji kai risouzou?
I spent all those days chasing my ideal image
oikaketa hibi
Play an F chord with distortion
F koodo kakinarasun da disutooshon
So loud that the needle swings off the scale
boryuumu wo furikiru yo
Subtitle source: neoHEVC
https://nyaa.si/view/1678808