Ookina shiroi kyanbasu ni kyokou no koraaju wo haru yo
I'm going to make a collage of fiction, and put it up on a big white canvas
Doko kara demo kirei ni utsuru, kochou sareta tenshi ga ita yo
There was a exaggerated angel that looked stunning from every angle
Cubism
Translation: Tsuyukikira & weightedangelcube
Romanization: PotatoAlien
Barahito yuganda tasashiku nakutemo mieta
Even if the rose person was distorted and not correct I could also see it
Ikiru tame tachiyotta bijutsukan no sezannu ni
At the Cezanne museum where I stopped to live
Nan mo wakannaina, mada shirazu ni ite mo kaketa
Even while not knowing anything, I could still draw
Aka zutto nurikonda, baka, kitto sou datta
But I ended up painting it all red, stupid, I know I did
Hidoi fude no kaiga, dakedo soko ga ii na
It's a terrible brushstroke, but that's what I like about it
Kudaranai sen dana, sono mama, aa
It's really a stupid line, just the way it is, ah
Kitte hatta kawa (Kitte hatta kawa), saite mieta aza (Aza)
My skin that was cut and pasted, my bruises seen when I was ripped open
La-la, la-la-la-la, warauyou ni, uita (Uita), abara
La-la, la-la-la-la, my ribs float, as if they're laughing
Gyutte daita kara (Gyutte daita kara), datte naita kara (Kara)
The sky that I held tight, because I had cried
La-la, la-la-la-la, nageku kabe ni
La-la, la-la-la-la, on the wall of grief
Kaita, Paburo Pikaso
I paint, like Pablo Picasso
Nazeka watashi no koto danatte nagame chatta yo
I don't know while looking at it I thought it was about me
Kore ga hoshii natte kanjita no
I felt like I wanted it
Sezannu no e wo kibonnu
I wanted a painting by Cezanne
Nante ne
Oh my god
Roujin ga tonari de jitto miteta yo
An old man was standing next to me and staring...
Giman, uso, wakasa naraba
To those who are young
Honmono no imi aru no kana
There's no meaning to deception and lies
Shinjitsu idaita mama
If I held the truth in my arms
Kusariochite yuka de shindeta (Chiin)
I'd rot away, dead on the floor (Ding)
Aka zutto nurikonda, yappa zutto yokatta
I painted the whole thing red, and to no surprise, it turned out much better
Iyarashii sen dana, ima mou, aa
This line disgusts me now, ah
Kitte hatta kawa (Kitte hatta kawa), saite chitta hana (Hana)
My skin that was cut and pasted, my bruises seen when I was ripped open
La-la, la-la-la-la, warauyou ni, mieta (Mieta), karada
La-la, la-la-la-la, my ribs float, as if they're laughing
Gyutte daita kara (Gyutte daita kara), datte naita kara (Kara)
The sky that I held tight, because I had cried
La-la, la-la-la-la, nageku kabe ni
La-la, la-la-la-la, on the wall of grief
Kaita, Paburo Pikaso
I paint, like Pablo Picasso
Watashi, uso no Pikaso
I'm the Picasso of lies