Subtitles: DeerGod
Alternative subtitles are available
Switch to English (United States) to view them
This is a work of fiction. All the characters, places, and businesses shown are fictitious. Any resemblance to reality is purely coincidental.
These fair maidens who flock
to the garden of Fudou Myou-ou,
smiles as spotless
as those of Shinsengumi soldiers,
once again cross the banks
of the Tama River.
Their unsullied bodies and hearts
clad in school uniforms of pure white.
Taking care not to ruffle
the pleats of their skirts...
...or dishevel their blue sailor collars,
they walk slowly,
as dictated by local customs.
Tokyo Metropolitan Hinominami High School...
A true garden of maidens.
(Addendum: It's co-ed.)
Good morning, dear viewers!
Deer!
Deer, deer, deer!
Nyun
Shikanoko's doe-eyed nonchalance, Koshi-tan's tale of vigilance
Shikanoko's doe-eyed nonchalance, Koshi-tan's tale of vigilance (nyun nyun)
Doe eyes popping up here and there without a care
Antlers jamming out, and the body of a girl?!
It's the craze that's in the latest rumors
Let's see what you can do, greenhorn!
"They've been found in Japan since ancient times."
Deer crackers? I'll take a lifetime supply!
Reindeer are comrades, wild goats are bovines
but together, we're all even-toed ungulates!
Gracefully dancing the nyun step...
Until the dawn breaks!
One, two, three!
Even with a life of ruminating, nyunyunyun
you can never predict deer-tinted days!
Avant-garde is perfect, the chaos will only deepen!
You'll get hooked before you know it, nyunyunyun
on the chaos & nonsense, deer-tinted days!
Bring on the unprecedented!
Anything goes, there's no rules here
Your smile always fills me with energy
Could you be m-m-my promised deer?!
With my vigilance hidden deep in my heart
I want to be with you forever!
Shikanoko's doe-eyed nonchalance, Koshi-tan's tale of vigilance!
GIRL MEETS DEER
It's still so cold out today!
Rained yesterday, too.
Be careful not to slip.
Are you okay?
Ah! Umm...
Thank you so much!
You're welcome.
Koshi Torako,
a second-year at Hinominami High.
President of the student council,
and class rep for class 2-B.
Not to mention... a stunning beauty, a student with
outstanding grades, and a well-rounded athlete.
Miss High School
2nd Semester Finals   Top 50
1: Koshi Torako, 500
2: Nekoyamada Neko, 499
3: Kitsunezaka Tsune, 490
4: Komai Koma, 489
5: Todaya Uta, 485
6: Kumagai Kuma, 480
The quintessential perfect girl,
whether at school or around town.
She's wonderful!
Exactly as planned!
Though her school life
may appear perfect,
Koshi Torako keeps a secret
she mustn't speak to anyone.
She is a former delinquent!
The Vicious Beast of Hino, Tokyo! That's me!
My dark days as a delinquent
too obsessed with shounen manga!
If my secret got out,
all that work making a clean break with high school
and becoming an honor student...
...would go down the drain!
Anyway, my disguise is flawless.
No one will ever see through it!
Or so she thought...
Until this very day.
Wait, the first episode starts
with someone hanging themselves?!
Thank god this is a late-night anime!
This is definitely not good, though!
P-Police? Doctor?
Conan-kun! Wait, no...
Hajime-chan!
Huh? She's alive?
What's going on?
If this isn't a suicide,
why is she hanging there?
Are those antlers?
Ah, they're those things they sell at Toky—
I mean, Chiba Mouseyland...
Wait! Shouldn't they have
come off and let her fall?!
Does this mean
they're real antlers?!
And they're probably deer antlers...
What kind of deer even are you?!
But come to think of it,
aren't male deer the ones with antlers?
Male
Female
UMA
Deergirl
Is she some kind of new UMA, then?
Or maybe a mutant
from some evil organization?!
Paranormal
Deergirl
Either way, that's a lot of snot...
It is twelve degrees Celsius.
Gah! That's disgusting!
And while I was lost in thought,
a bunch of animals showed up to dine on her corpse!
Huh? Want summa this?
You want a piece of me, huh?! Ora Ora Ora!
Want some?! Ora Ora Ora!
Why is she trying to pick a fight
in her situation?
Should I try to help?
She's staring a hole through my head!
So intense!
If I get caught up in all this,
I'll be late for school!
An honor student like me
absolutely cannot be late!
I'll just... pretend I didn't see her...
...and hurry to school...
You're leaving me...
You're really gonna
abandon me like this.
I-I-I-I would never!
I was just about to...
Actually, this is your fault
for hanging there, right?
I'm in a hurry.
I don't have time for playing games...
Tomorrow's news will say,
"Hino City high schooler caught on electric cables dies."
Every morning,
when you walk through this street,
you'll see my face.
"If only I had helped her when I could"...
You'll spend the rest of your life haunted by regret.
All right, already! I get it!
I live!
She's freakin' heavy!
How the—
Would you be so kind as to tell me
how you ended up there?
I woke up this morning and was just,
like, there, y'know? Somehow.
Seriously! Tell me!
However it happened, thank you so much
for helping me, Miss Delinquent!
Oh, I didn't do anything special—
Miss Delinquent?
Huh?! Who're you callin' a delinquent?!
You, miss!
Wh-What are you talking about?!
Me? One as beautiful
and elegant as a peony?
A delinquent?! Th-That's absurd!
That so? Hmm...
But I smell it all over you...
Smell what?
And my antlers are reacting to you.
Wait, what kind of sensors are those?!
Being near her is way too risky...
A-Are you sure you aren't imagining things?
Perhaps you're mistaken...
Oh, I have to get going!
Try not to get caught up there again, okay?
That was close...
My disguise should have been flawless...
How did she...?
What was with that girl?
Everyone, take your seats!
Today, we have a new transfer student
I would like you to meet.
A transfer student?
I got a bad feeling about this...
Come on in!
Coming!
I knew it!
Oh? Huh?
H-How are you stuck again?
Learn your lesson, already!
Nyun!
You're kidding me, right?!
Now, Shikanoko-san,
introduce yourself.
Shikanoko Noko
Lersant! I'm Shikanoko Noko!
You can call me Noko-tan!
Noko-tan!
What a funny girl.
She's a deer!
Why is she getting a normal welcome?
Am I the weirdo here?
And you can sit...
Oh, there's a free seat
next to Koshi-san!
A common trope in school anime:
the conveniently free seat.
This is bad!
If she says anything weird,
my high school life is over!
I have to get ahead of this!
G-Good morning!
Oh, it's you!
So you're a transfer student, huh?
I'm Koshi Torako.
If you have any questions,
don't hesitate to ask!
Thanks!
Huh? Is this actually
gonna work out somehow?
Guess I had nothing to
worry about after all!
You can call me whatever you like.
Whatever I like?
I was just overthinking things...
Got it!
Miss Delinquent!
Miss Delinquent! Miss Delinquent!
I hope we'll get along,
Miss Delinquent!
Koshi-san is a delinquent?!
Her of all people?!
We misheard that, right?!
Hey!
None of you batted an eye at the deer transfer student!
How does this surprise you?!
A d-d-delinquent? Me?
What are you talking about?
Could you please not make things up?
My animal instincts tell me
you're a delinquent.
Are you a wild beast?!
Furthermore...
You're a virgin, aren't you?
Huh?
Huh?!
I mean, my antlers are reacting to you!
What kind of system
do you have going there?!
So Koshi-san's a virgin?
I knew she had to be!
Really?!
Stay out of this, peanut gallery!
Wh-What kind of proof
do you have to claim I'm a virgin...?
Huh? So you're not a virgin?
Well, that's... uh...
Virginity confirmed!
VIRGIN
Toudai-ji,
Nara Park
Koufuku-ji,
It's Koshi-san!
As beautiful as always!
My disgraceful past
nearly got exposed back there...
I have to keep this up...
But I can't let my guard down!
I need to make sure that deer
doesn't expose me as a former delinquent!
Which is why...
...I have to get ahead of her
before she says more weird—
Huh?
A giant pile of sweets on my desk?
Huh?!
Wait, no! That cross-shaped wrapping...
Those are deer crackers!
Deer crackers.
Known as soul food
for the people of Nara prefecture.
(Addendum: So says one theory.)
Students on school trips
commonly try them for laughs...
...but much like their taste,
these jokes are dry and bland.
The only one who would do this is...
It must have been her!
Wait, is she drooling?
What is she, a merlion?
Umm, Shikanoko-san?
What's all of this about?
Nyun? Recompense?
Your face tells a different story!
Miss!
You saved me this morning,
didn't you?
It's my thanks.
Hmm? Oh, that was nothing.
No need to thank me...
What? Deer crackers
not good enough for you?
That's not the issue...
And why do you sound
so cocky all of a sudden?
You want one of my antlers
as a special gift?
They come off?!
Here.
I don't want it!
By the way, they're edible.
Wh-What do they taste like?
Not that I'll try one...
They're tasteless, odorless, and super tough!
You're saying I'd have to force it down?!
If you must insist...
Just this once.
I told you, I don't want it!
And, like, not that I should argue,
but aren't you abandoning your identity too quickly?!
Without antlers,
you're just an ordinary high school girl!
You saved my life...
I'll forsake my entire character for you!
That's too serious!
It's too early to break character!
This is still the first episode,
you know.
Don't want deer crackers...
Don't want antlers...
They reattach...
Ah! Then what you really want...
...is my tender deer flesh?!
Venison
Why are you so wrapped up
with this deer thing?
I get it now!
Go ahead and eat me!
I'm not gonna eat you!
And who are these people?!
I mean, I don't have
anything else to give you!
Look! As you can see,
I have no money.
But you had more deer crackers?
Please, don't make me
give up more...
Why are you acting
like I'm extorting you or something?
And for crackers of all things!
Oops! I let my real side slip!
Hey, Noko-tan!
Do you and Koshi-san know each other?
You've been acting like good friends all day!
Huh?! Wait, Noko-tan?
My nickname. Cute, isn't it?
She's so annoying...
You see, I got stuck on a power line
this morning, and Miss Delinq—
Shikanoko-san! I just remembered,
our teacher wants to see you!
No running in school hallways
Oh my, Koshi-tan...
Why did you bring me here all of a sudden?
Out of order
- The student council
How bold...
What are you imagining?!
Huh? Real question is,
what were you imagining, Koshi-tan?
Huh?!
W-Well, I mean... I-I wasn't...
Koshi-tan...
Bona fide virgin.
Will you shut up?!
And why do you keep calling me Koshi-tan?
It's a nickname.
Doesn't "Noko-tan and Koshi-tan" sound nice?
What are we, a comedy duo?!
Besides, who said you could nickname me?
Okay, Miss Delinq—
Koshi-tan's fine.
She's accepted it.
I mean, it doesn't really matter, anyway.
Can you promise me that you'll never,
ever reveal my true identity?
Nyun?
I'm passing as an honor student here,
so it will be a big problem if anyone finds out.
If you speak a word of this...
There's gonna be hell to pay.
Understand?
Your real identity...
You mean that you're actually a virgin?
You're wro—Well, not wrong,
but that's not what I meant!
Dammit...
You just won't stop calling me out...
Stupid brat!
Stick to the antler gags, will ya?!
Of course...
These antlers are weird, aren't they?
Indoors
O-Oh... I...
I mean, of course a girl who
grows antlers is creepy, right?
Like, what even is a deer anyway
when you really think about it?
I'm sorry if I touched a nerve!
I see... She's probably always
getting laughed at because of her appearance,
and yet I...
I'm a failure of a honor student!
No... A failure of a human being!
I-I'm sorry!
I don't mind the antlers at all!
So? This is better, huh?
What...?
Koshi-tan wanted to know where
the antlers began, but she feared the answer.
Today's been exhausting...
I need to hurry home and prep
for tomorrow's classes...
What was that noise?
Was it from over there?
Excuse me! Is anyone there?
I just heard a loud noise.
Is everything oka—
Deer
P-Police? Doctor?
Conan-kun... Wait, no. Hajime-chan!
Nyun, Koshi-tan!
Sh-Sh-Shikanoko-san, is that b-b-blood?
Did something happen?
Oh, my bad!
I fell off the stepladder
and scraped my knee!
No, your head!
Your freakin' head!
What a cute bandage!
Shut up! What are you doing
in this unused warehouse, anyway?
I was cleaning!
Cleaning? By yourself?
Yep! Thanks, Koshi-tan!
All right, back to work!
Nyun?
Okay, okay. I'll help you.
What? For real?
W-Well, you're hurt,
and who knows what you'll do
if I leave you alone...
Yippee! Thanks!
She is undeniably a tsundere.
Cleaning is is a lot of work,
but you look like you're having fun, huh?
Well, yeah.
I'm doing it with you, Koshi-tan.
Y-You're too much!
We're just cleaning!
I guess even cleaning can be fun
if you do it with others!
Oh my, it looks so much cleaner already!
Ms. Ukai?
Ms. Ukai, lersant!
Hey there! Lersant!
So you've been helping out, Koshi-san?
Thank you! It must have been difficult.
Oh, not at all! It was nothing!
I feel much better knowing you'll be
joining the Deer Club too, Koshi-san!
Of cour—
Excuse me? Deer Club?
Well, as promised,
you can use this space however you like.
Hooray!
Wait, what the heck is a Deer Club?
And why am I joining?!
What? You don't know?
I founded the Deer Club!
What is this avant-garde sounding club?!
I promised that if she cleaned up in here,
she could use it as a clubroom.
Right?
Don't give me that "Right?" crap!
This won't end well for me
if I get sucked into this pointless club!
Oh, it's such a relief!
You're so reliable
and compassionate, Koshi-san.
Like an older sister!
With how cheerful and kind you are,
I'm sure this will be an enjoyable club!
It'll be like home for us!
You're so smart too,
so maybe you'll even win an award!
Maybe even make it to nationals!
If you join, I'm sure the Deer Club
will do incredible things!
You can count on me!
Koshi-tan was easily persuaded.
Okay, Shikanoko-san,
make sure you fill out the club approval form.
Nyun!
Club name: Deer Club.
Club president: Koshi Torako.
Activities: Taking care of deer, mostly.
Wait a minute!
Why am I the club president?
Because you're the president, Koshi-tan.
Because you're the president, Koshi-san.
Huh? Am I the weirdo here?
Isn't this the Deer Club?
If Shikanoko-san, a literal deer,
can't be president, then who can?
Oh, that's what you meant?
Look, it says here that the deer club's activities are
"taking care of deer, mostly", right?
Huh? Yeah...
Club member
I'll be the Deer Club's
resident deer, you see...
The Deer Club's resident deer?!
Deer
The president is responsible for her care!
That's you, Koshi-tan!
I am not okay with this!
What kind of club takes care of deer, anyway?
Is this an agricultural school?!
Here, submitted.
And accepted!
Whoa! You work too fast!
Well, then, madam president,
I'm counting on you to look after Shikanoko-san.
Take good care of me, nyun!
All right...
Because she said "leave it to me"
with such a wide smile,
Koshi-tan found herself unable to argue.
Deer Club - New members wanted!
The Deer Club's inaugurated! Hooray!
What an unexpected turn of events
for just one day...
I'll bring more deer crackers tomorrow!
Oh well.
Now, then, can you start by
giving me a good brushing?
You can't be serious!
And what's with
that scrub brush thingy?
It's for animals.
Fine, guess I have no choice!
Lersant!
Dammit, why me of all people?
Ugh, you're going to make me do this
every club meeting, aren't you?
Curse you, foul beast!
S-So scary!
I don't know what's going on,
but the Deer Club's battle
has only just begun!
A bustling crowd of gathering deer
Where did they even come from, all these deer
Deer, deer, deer are all that's here!
Do those deer crackers really taste so great?
Round and golden brown, don't tease me with them...
Why ever would you really want them that bad?
Deer, deer, deer!
Are there smarts inside all those deer?
How come they always know if we have them?
Deer, deer, deer are all that's here!
Come rain, come sun, it's all for the deer