Who am I?
In the middle of the night
Your pity erases my name
In the unwavering surface of the water,
a hidden scenery lies in wait
Unaware of that,
Even if I end up turning into mist
the clouds drifted by
I should be okay with that,
I should be able to say
it makes no difference to me
Until yesterday,
the clouds drifted by
Why do I always fall right away
While searching for
someone's hand to grab?
While admiring the sky
as much as I am able
I'm
the
I'm the rain
that understands it will be repelled
The rain that can't come to resemble any person
Rain
Sun
Cloud
Because I know so little of the pain that troubles the rest of the world
I am the rain blurring the world
The rain, guided by the dawn
Cloudy
Until I know the hidden taste of the ocean that washed ashore
North
South
West
East
The thunder which
blocks out the stars
And the cumulonimbus
clouds just out of sight
As much as I could,
as much as I could,
as much as I could
I wanted to part from them
As much as I could,
as much as I could,
as much as I could
I wanted to part from them
There's no time to
put up an umbrella
Still, I think I'll probably
be okay like this
But because I still don't understand,
I end up soaking wet
Under the night's heavy rain,
I open my eyes
I'm the rain
tracing the world
The raindrops
you don't notice for the downpour
Rain
I discover the stars
adorning the night sky
Floating in the sky, leaving my mark upon the earth
Almost disappearing, completely overflowing
Even if it could be captured in ink, nothing would have come from it
The world's temperature is shifting
the
I'm
I'm the rain
that understands that it will fall
The rain that can't come to resemble any person
But I want to know the feelings that trouble the rest of the world
I'm the rain blurring the world
The rain, guided by the dawn
Until I come to embody the hidden taste of the ocean that washed ashore
I'm the rain
R
ai
n
I'm The Rain
Music
inabakumori
Rain
Umbrella
Art & Animation
Nukunuku Nigirimeshi
Video
inabakumori
English Translation
JaysAndRavens47
with edits by Thai1210
via Vocaloid Lyrics Wiki
Other translations
ChatGPT
Until you arrive
Don't forget all that I
taught you
Facing each other in the
midst of a tranquil ocean
Stand a different scenery
and a familiar form—
an answer waiting
for approval