On the count of three:
Venture into our secret garden!
Hey Onii- I mean, Mahiro! Wanna try on a maid outfit?
No, no, no, we're doing a bunny girl costume!
Huh?
Let's put on matching dresses!
H-Hold on!
Hey! Stop it!
Either way, take off your clothes!
NOOOOOO!
Ethics rejected, drug perfected
(Something's afoot)
No trace of resistance detected!
(Gone, kaput)
Cutie acquired, cuddling frenzy
(Deary me)
Partner recaptured, time to get busy!
(Teehee)
Let's throw a sleepover, yay, yay, yay
(Mahiro's got himself a harem!)
A night of unbridled girl-on-girl action
(I'm getting kinda turned on)
On the count of three:
Let's get that heart a-throbbin'
One little push is all that's needed
To ease your transition into a new world!
(One! Two! Three!)
(Go bouncy world!)
Fine, whatever, totally beat
Just forget it, surrender complete
Girls contain huge secrets
Within their tiny bodies!
Do your best, go all the way
As your reality starts to fray
Girl power makes the world go round!
My impending identity crisis is officially on hold
Subtitle source: Okay-Subs
https://nyaa.si/view/1654825