kuraku semai no ga suki data
I liked dark, cramped spaces,
so I'd bury my face deep in my hood
fukaku kaburu fuudo no naka
My eyes resented the heartless world,
mujou na sekai wo uranda me wa
but yearned for love
dou shiyou mo naku ai wo ho shiteta
I liked being soaked by the rain,
ame ni nureru no ga suki data
because my face looked better clouded over
kumotta kao ga niau kara
I pretended to be afraid of the storm
arashi ni obieteru furi wo shite
while waiting for the sky to burst
sora ga wareru no wo matteitan da
Strum through the light's distortion
kakinarase hikari no fazu de
I want to make thunder roar
raimei wo todorokasetain da
Drum beyond the pain
uchinarase itami no saki e
What can I do?
dou shiyou?
This fierce pounding is out of control
daibousou doumou na kodou wo
Strum in a harmonizing quartet
kakinarase majiwaru karutetto
I want to cause a revolution
kakumei wo nashitogetemitai na
Drum in a lamenting forte
uchinarase nageki no fuorute
What can I do?
dou shiyou?
My savage nature is beyond wild
chou honpou kyoubou na honshou wo
Subtitle source: neoHEVC
https://nyaa.si/view/1678808