Subtitles: DeerStalker
Alternative subtitles are available
Switch to English (United States) to view them
Oh, shoot!
This is a work of fiction. All characters, places, and businesses shown are fictitious. Any resemblance to reality is purely coincidental.
I got sidetracked and ended up running late!
Deer Club
Sorry for the wait!
Cam 1
Cam 2
Cam 3
Cam 4
A-A deer!
shikanoko nokonoko koshitantan
Shikanoko's doe-eyed nonchalance, Koshi-tan's tale of vigilance
shikanoko tokotoko arawaru nokonoko
Little deer's here and there without a care
tsunotsuno pyokopyoko mitame wa onnya no ko
Antlers jutting out of her hair, though she's a girl all too fair?!
chikagoro uwasa no nakanaka kiwamono
She's become quite the affair
otenami ikahodo hena choko
Let's see what you've got, ya little square!
sugoku mukashi kara Japan ni seisoku
Been in Japan since the olden days
shika senbei nara mugen ni kudasai
If you've got deer crackers, I'll take a million!
tonakai wa nakama kamoshika wa ushika
Reindeer are just fine, goats may be bovine...
demo demo matomete guuteimoku
But hey, we've all got our hooves!
nun no step de odorou
Let us dance the nyun step...
'till the crack of dawn!
yo ga akeru made
One, two, three!
nando datte hansuu shite nununun
Try as you might, nyunyunyun
yosoku fukanou shikairo days
you'll never predict our fawn-filled days!
Avant-garde's darn right, only more chaos to be had!
avant-garde de all right chaos mashi mashi
itsu no ma ni kuse ni natte nununun
You'll soon be right at home, nyunyunyun
hacha de mecha na shikairo days
with our chaotic, fawn-filled days!
hatenkou bacchi come on
Delusional lunacy, come on!
nandemo ari rule nante nashi
Anything goes, no rules here, comrade!
kimi no egao de genki mantan
Your smile brightens my day in one glance
moshikashite unmei no ma ma my deer
Could this be fate, m-m-my deer?!
kokoro no dokoka de koshitantan
I swear by my inner vigilance
kimi to nara itsu ma demo
I'll always be with you!
shikanoko nokonoko koshitantan
Shikanoko's doe-eyed nonchalance, Koshi-tan's tale of vigilance!
Enter Bashame
W-W-Why is there a deer here?!
Well, I suppose for the Deer
Club, it isn't that strange...
Deer Club
If anything, seeing them around
has become completely ordinary.
How did I not notice until now?
Deer
Crackers
Either way, don't eat our deer
crackers like you own the place!
Hey, Shikanoko!
This a friend of yours?
Where is she?
Wait! Could it be...?!
Shikanoko!
What are you trying to pull?!
I already know it's you, Shikanoko!
Take that thing off already!
She's not listening?
That girl thinks she can mess with me, huh?
She's got guts. I'll give her that.
I'm tearing that ridiculous
disguise of hers right off!
Take it off! Take that stupid costume off!
Did you seriously think I wouldn't catch on?!
Deer Club
Boy, I sure am parched...!
It's such a long ways from
the school building to here!
Oh, right! I bought something real nice earlier!
Ta-da!
Two XL servings of our school's
Limited Edition Springtime
Sakuramochi-flavored Tapioca Milk Tea!
It's too bad a regular old deer can't have any!
You poor thing!
And here I had one for you too!
Since you can't drink these,
I guess I have them all to myself!
You cool with that? I'll be having your share!
She doesn't care?!
Damn. Looks like it'll take more
than tapioca to get her to crack.
Manjiro!
Deer are herbivores.
They eat grass and leaves.
My beloved little Manjiro is gonna be deer food!
Koshi-tan fosters every decorative plant in the
club room and lovingly named them all herself.
Iruka
Umako
Emishi
Don't eat him, you stupid deer!
What in the world is that noise?! I've never heard anything like it!
When provoked, male deer first
intimidate by uttering a deep groan.
One should stay clear until they calm down.
Not backing down, huh?
Well, I can't afford to either.
Manjiro and the others' lives are in my hands!
Guess I'll have to use force!
Have a taste of your inane water bottle weakness!
Noko-tan is deathly afraid of water bottles.
How's that? You can't move a muscle!
If you want me to get rid of
them, that disguise has to go!
What?!
T-This girl!
When did she overcome her fear of water bottles?!
If I don't think of something quick,
Manjiro and the others are goners!
Is there anything I can use to distract her? Think!
T-That's it!
Secret
S-So that's where my notebook full
of my deepest darkest secrets was!
Secret
I really should torch this
shameful past of mine already!
Glance.
Secret
But come to think of it, Shikanoko
and I are such close friends now!
If she'd only drop her disguise, she might
get a little peek before it's gone forever!
This thing's so embarrassing,
I can't even leave it back home.
I can't believe lugging it around
everywhere is finally going to come in handy!
Still, if I'm gonna sink
this low, I'm sure she'll...
Bingo! Hook, line, and sinker!
Time to seal the deal!
S-She might even get to hear all those ridiculous
songs that I came up with way back when, too!
What, really?! Lemme hear, lemme hear!
Oh, if you insist! Just one, okay?!
One, two, three, four.
Go get 'em, newly reborn Koshi-tan!
I can hear the winds of sadness!
Might someone be weeping away?
Behind the school building at dusk!
The starving tiger's territory!
An untouchable sanctuary!
If you aren't careful, she'll bite your head off!
However, I can't just ignore someone singing
so sorrowfully! I'll wipe those tears right away!
My, my. And here I was trying not to stand out!
Three minutes?
Three seconds is plenty!
Go! Fight! Koshi-tan!
I might be reformed, but I'm
still a force to be reckoned with!
This tiger's fist will smash
your face to smoldering pieces!
A tiger's paw ain't so soft, y'know?
When you're crying, let yourself be heard!
Koshi-tan! Koshi-tan!
I am the reborn Koshi-tan!
Now for the second verse! Let's go!
Go get 'em, newly reborn Koshi-tan!
Woah there! I almost forgot
not to perform more than one.
Huh? That's too bad!
Sorry, no can do!
Until you take that thing off, I won't...
I wanna hear more!
Let's hear another round of
the reborn Koshi-tan's song!
Sh-Shikanoko?
There're two of you? W-Why?!
Two of me? What're you
talking about, Koshi-tan?
I'm talking about that! That!
They can communicate?
He says he came here after
escaping from the Hino Zoo.
E-Escaping?
Maybe the scent of all these
deer crackers led him here.
What the hell?!
By the way, what's with this notebook?
Oh! There's that original song from earlier!
C'mon, keep going!
Go get 'em, newly reborn Koshi-tan!
Koshi-tan's desire to crawl in a hole was so overwhelming,
she decided to skip finding one altogether and dig it herself.
Lersant! Take caribou!
Lersant.
And so, the deer went on its
way back to the Hino Zoo.
Kinkasan
Koganeyama Shrine
Sanrikufukkou
National Park
Entrance
Ceremony​
Under the sun's warm embrace,
cherry blossoms burst into full bloom.
To all of our new students,
congratulations on your first day here!
On behalf of the student body, I'd like
to offer you all a heartfelt welcome.
Spring.
Koshi-tan's class enters its third year.
Seems there're no patented
Sazae-san time warps at play here.
I wish I got to see Koshi-tan's
student council president speech.
I'll bet you were pretty cool up there, huh?
You bet I was.
Woah! Hang on!
Are you okay?!
Why are you here of all places?
What's wrong?! Are you sick?!
Shall I take you to the nurse's office?!
Or do I need to call an ambulance?!
Maybe even the police?!
The JSDF?!
Looks like ol' Bashame here felt a
bit too warm and fell right asleep.
I-Is that so?
Bashame?
I'm just glad you're feeling okay.
But what are you doing here?
You're a new student, aren't you?
Bashame came here to meet you!
Huh?
Ba
Sha
Me
Bashame is Bashame Meme, a first year.
Bashame looks up to you so much,
she just couldn't wait to meet you!
Ukai-sensei told Bashame
you'd be here, so here she is!
So, you were so captivated by the wonderful honor student
at the entrance ceremony that you came to see her?
Bashame wants to be just like you!
So, please, please let Bashame be your disciple!
Sorry, but no can do.
Not that I don't appreciate it...
Shikanoko-senpai!
"Shikanoko-senpai"?
W-What?! Her, and not me?!
Who might you be?
I just gave that entrance speech you heard earlier!
I'm the student council president, dangit!
Bashame wanted to meet Shikanoko-senpai,
so she waited right here!
Is this girl nuts or something?
Bashame-san, why'd you pick this dolt—
Er, Shikanoko-san, to look up to?
Glad you asked!
Before the entrance ceremony started,
I was passed out in front of the school gate.
Why?
My tummy is so grumbly.
Bashame is done for.
The entrance ceremony is
going to start without me.
Bashame will die before she
even makes her high school debut.
Want it?
Thank you very much.
Later, then.
Ah, please wait!
Um, what's your name?!
I haven't done anything worth remembering.
And so, Shikanoko-senpai is the
one who Bashame owes her life to.
A deer cracker saved your life?
After that, Bashame found herself thinking
throughout the whole entrance ceremony...
What an amazing role model.
Bashame wants to be just like her.
Bashame wants to be a deer like her!
You want to be a deer?
That's why Bashame has to become your disciple!
You want to be her disciple...
Why are there even more
butterflies swarming you?!
Lersant.
Hey, what do we do about this girl?
The name was Bashame, was it not?
Yes! Bashame here!
Do you truly have the resolve to become a deer?
What's with that tone?!
What do you mean resolve to become a deer?!
Yes! Bashame will do all
it takes to become a deer!
What kind of class is this?!
I suppose that means you'll have
to enlist in the Deer Club first!
Of course! Bashame will join the Deer Club!
Could you two stop ignoring every word I say?!
The president of the Deer Club
is Koshi-tan, our caretaker.
Thus, you should be asking for
Koshi-tan to look after you, not me.
Yes, ma'am! Understood!
Listen to your caretaker!
Wait, what is this?
Now that I'm out of middle school, I finally
get to attend the same school as Onee-chan!
And with my application to the Deer Club, I'll be able
to spend every waking moment of my life with her!
I can do this and that to her all that I want!
Onee-chan!
Koshi-tan-senpai, please allow
Bashame to bask in your care as well.
Wait! Don't!
Onee-chan?!
Anko?!
What are you doing with another woman?!
Hooray. The Deer Club has
gained two new members.
Kinkasan as
seen from
Gobanshoyama
It took a lot to get there, but
we now have four club members.
The Deer Club has finally become an official club!
Up until now, it didn't feel like
anything more than a way to kill time,
but I feel like we can really
push the envelope now!
All right, you guys!
Starting today, we're gonna go all out!
Shikanoko Noko
3rd Year
Status...
Deer
An
Koshi
Matching cups with Onee-chan.
Koshi Anko
1st Year
Status...
Self-Proclaimed
Onee-chan Caretaker
An
Koshi
Bashame Meme
1st Year
Status...
More Human
Than Deer
Yum!
Koshi Torako
3rd Year
Status...
Club Prez/
Caretaker
I can't let things stay like this!
It's time to fix the Deer Club.
Deer Club
Meeting!
And so, we're having our first
Deer Club Strategy Meeting.
Now there's a start.
You're so cute when you're serious!
Quiet down there!
A new term just started,
yet you lot are loafing around!
Do you hold no respect for the Deer Club at all?!
As for what there is to respect...
Do you really want me to answer that?
I'm so disappointed.
The Deer Club I worked so hard to build....
It's...
If others find out about our indolent club activities...
Our budget'll go down the gutter!
Even my hard-earned position as head
of the student council will crumble away!
Learning that Koshi-tan used to be a
delinquent was already quite the shock,
but knowing that she's this
blunt is downright hilarious!
Yet another of her charms!
Deer Club
Meeting!
We can't keep going like this!
Each of you needs to decide
on a solid goal to work towards!
Okay!
First up, Shikanoko!
Deer Club
Meeting!
As the club's main representative, and
for the sake of your status as senior deer,
set an example for our
kouhai and state your goal!
I suppose so. My goal...
Oh!
I wanna bathe in a tub full of deer crackers!
Absolutely not.
Syunyun. Shot down.
Do you intend to spend our
whole budget on deer crackers?!
Proposal rejected!
Take this seriously!
Another goal of mine, huh...
I got nothing.
Wasn't the Deer Club your idea?!
Why did you even start it?!
This girl's hopeless.
It's like she's trying
to set a bad example!
Deer Club
Meeting!
Next up, deer apprentice Bashame!
Don't cook rice in the club room!
Koshi-tan-senpai, want some?
I don't!
You're the one who said she
wanted to become a deer!
Surely you have some sort of goal in mind!
I guess so.
Bashame wants to make her own rice paddy!
Wuzzat?
A-A rice paddy?
I'd take any field, really.
No. I still don't follow.
Bashame realized something.
Us deer need to scrape by in the
harsh savannah that is modern society,
and the key to that is self-sufficiency!
As such, we'll start by erecting
a rice field next to the club room!
Bashame will cultivate her rice
just as any proud deer would!
What do you think a deer is?!
Let's look forward to autumn.
Deer Club
Meeting!
I swear, it's nothing but nonsense with you all.
It's all up to you, Anko!
You're the only one I can trust here!
Let's see.
I joined the Deer Club so that I could help you, so...
Staying by your side and supporting
you in any way I can, I suppose?
Anko...! That's my little sister!
You really are the only one I can rely on!
If I can manage it, I'd love to make it so
you can't possibly live without me either!
Yikes! Give me back that praise
I showered you with three seconds ago!
Deer Club
Meeting!
What's your goal then, Koshi-tan?
Unlike you all, I've thought this through!
What is it?
I've got plenty of goals, but the first one is...
The first one?
I want to make the club room cuter!
I think you've done enough there...
No, this building used to be
an old storehouse, you see.
I'd like to rebuild it cuter than ever.
Doesn't Koshi-tan's goal have the
absolute least to do with the Deer Club?
Is it okay for the student council head
to have such a conflict of interest?
Seems like a pitch we should shelve.
I-Is it really that bad for
the club room to look nice?!
Plus, isn't it my responsibility to make sure that
the deer passing through have a nice environment?!
If that's the case, you should let
me have my deer cracker bath!
And Bashame's rice paddy!
And let me live out my fantasies of doing
this and that with you in the club room!
How come Anko's the only one who shifted gears?!
Frankly, you're the one who's in the wrong here!
The purpose of the Deer Club
is to take care of deer in need!
As the caretaker, you need
to consider my needs more!
If you're gonna be like this, I'm just gonna leave!
What?!
That'd take the "deer" right out
of the Deer Club, wouldn't it?
And then we'd just be another disbanded club.
Huh?
When they come knocking asking who's to blame,
we'd only be able to say it was her, wouldn't we?
Hey!
Before we discuss strategy or whatever, we need
to talk about the working conditions of the deer!
TREASURE
YOUR DEER!
Well, you do have one hell of a point...
Damn it.
Then, what do you want me to do?
TREASURE
YOUR DEER!
Brush me.
Well, that's reasonable.
TREASURE
YOUR DEER!
Here.
TREASURE
YOUR DEER!
Now, show me what you've got!
I see!
If you want to become a better deer,
a proper brushing is priority number one!
Bashame hears you loud and clear!
That's our Noko-tan-senpai!
No. I don't think she's trying
to teach you anything here.
Koshi-tan-senpai!
Bashame's hair is right here!
What?
Senpai, I don't care a lick about you,
but if you're saying you're gonna go the mile and
brush Bashame's hair, I'll take you right up on that!
Where'd all that sass come from?!
And I said nothing of the sort!
You two, or rather, you little does...
You don't know a thing about the Onee-chan of
mine who's taking such good care of you, do you?
The two of us have been practically married for 15 years.
I'm a far better fit for her than either of you greenhorns.
That's right. To be frank...
If there's anyone who should be
the Deer Club's resident deer, it's me!
When did you become a deer?!
What happened to the whole supporting me thing?!
So, Onee-chan, what say you?
You want to brush me far more
than those pests, don't you?
Don't you?
The pressure...!
We'll just have to hold a contest to
see who's the most fit to be our deer!
I'll gladly take you all on!
Bashame won't stand down!
This was supposed to be a meeting!
I'm the deer!
It's me!
Deer!
So this is the ever-troublesome Deer Club, huh?
warawara atsumaru shika
Hustling-bustling, all together, de-er!
dokokara kuru no ka shika
Where'd they come from, all these many de-er!
shika shika shika shika inai
Deer, deer, deer are all that's here!
sonna ni oishii shika senbei
Are those deer crackers really that great?
They're all too round and golden brown...
marukute kongari
jirasanaide
Don't tempt me, oh please!
doushite sonna ni hoshigaru no
Why, oh why, would one want them oh so badly?
shika shika shika
Deer, deer, deer!
atama ga ii no ka shika
Might they be geniuses, those deer?
How do they always know who has 'em?
motteru to bareru no naze
shika shika shika shika inai
Deer, deer, deer are all that's here!
harete mo ame demo shika no tame
Be it blazing, or even raining, we're here for the deer!