Kyu-kurarin
(Light-headed,
racing heart)
english tl
AngelSubs
via Vocaloid Lyrics Wiki
I squinted at
the wailing dial
Surely,
surely,
through the mirror
8 o'clock has
come and gone
My unamused
face hasn't
changed
I'm glad about
that
Beside the pink
flowerpot's
soaked heart
Is an overgrown,
swollen bud
entangled with it
It's so foolish
Ahh,
I'll turn into
a fossil
Ahh,
I want to keep
up the act
I have to smile,
Since I don't really
have anything
going for me
I can't fill this
gaping emptiness;
What will I do
if it all
gets out?
Ahh
The neighbor
to your right
My heart races,
head fuzzy
Say, when I fall asleep tonight
and open my eyes
I can't find
a single reason
to get up
When the morning comes,
what exactly...
...should I do?
I squinted
at the wailing dial
Backing away
one step
at a time
"See you tomorrow"
I mumble
Relief came
Before any
sort of joy
Through the
reminiscent
setting sun
The tiny cracks
can be seen
It's so
unbelievably
terrifying
Ahh,
You'll find out
I want to keep
up the act
I have to smile,
or the things
precious to me
will break
I wish for a
happy tomorrow,
But what will I
do about this
abyss of loneliness?
I can't even
scream anymore
My heart
seizes up,
head dizzy
Ahh, I want to think a sky
Filled with rainbows is pretty
What I yearn for
is being unable
to run away
What everyone
finds worthless
Ugh,
but there's
nothing to be
done about it
My heart races,
head fuzzy
The final days
are closing in
on me
This withered bud
is so unbelievably
filthy...
So innocent
Ahh,
I'll turn into
a curse
Ahh,
I have to say
"I've given up"
Or the static
in my head
won't stop
I can't fill
this gaping
emptiness;
What will I do
if it all gets out?
Ahh,
it's just like
she said,
It's over
Ahh,
I'll end up happy
losing things
is painful
If it all goes
to waste,
I'll take my
punishment
for having loved
You're so,
so nice...
What would I do
if I cried
into your chest?
That was the dream
I saw in the end
My heart
Hangs in the air