Wanna do this? Wanna do that? Wanna do anything?
It's like you're dead
Treading water doesn't win the race
But that's just more AI circulation
Today our story finally begins
Emotion like an unhatched egg
Out of shell hell and onto the griddle
And with a posed look on your face...
Ready, and...
This dream yearning for eternity
Is ended by the morning coming
I've cried so many tears of sugar
But at least now I see what I feel
Time cooked them into a bittersweet caramel,
The ribbon like a cursed armor wrapped tight
Only these feelings will ever understand these feelings I feel
Hand in hand, let's tackle it step by step
Our story, the promises we hold dear
A vibrantly checkered past, the story of poor me
Let's fill up these empty pages with a new chapter
Subtitle source: MTBB
https://nyaa.si/view/1852772