Lyrics & Music
siinamota
Art & Video
So, as for my life
—or, anyone's life
often times,
Sometimes, and
they're judged equally
...right?
You came into
my dark skies
bringing along
depression
With some
occasional rain,
but I'm so dependent
on you,
what do I do?
Love-hate to the
point of decay,
love-hate to the
But you take it
all in
and smile so easily
...why?
My written words
come out
ambiguous,
my written words
come out
ambiguous
They don't quite
convey what they
should, so I look to you
as the only one to trust
Collecting
the
dreams
I
threw
away
Because
of
a
little,
little
mistake
I
made
Ahh,
"even if at times
I stumble"
It’s so
cold,
cold
Cold,
cold,
cold
It’s so cold,
cold,
cold
—don't sweet
talk me
Ahh,
your,
your voice is
so far,
far,
far
So far,
far,
—don't hurt me
Do I care
where I am
on this line
in order for me,
to be me?
I'm here with
promises I've
recollected,
I'm here with
promises I've
recollected,
Too painful to
swallow the mistake
I had made that day
Love-hate to the
point of decay,
Here you are,
taking it all in,
smiling so easily...
why?
"A pair
of flowers
to settle
me down,"
Because,
because,
you've
given up?
Ahh,
dream so far away
running after that
It’s so fast,
fast,
fast
Fast,
fast,
fast
It’s so fast,
fast,
fast
—don't sweet talk me
Those feelings
I couldn't
drive away
I hate,
hate,
hate
Hate,
hate,
hate
hate it
—can't I be forgiven?
Ahh,
it should be
the dream,
the dream I had, but
I’m scared,
scared,
scared
Scared,
scared,
scared
I’m so scared,
scared,
scared
—don't come near me
We
just keep
repeating
our secret code
It’s so cold,
cold,
cold
cold, cold, cold, cold
cold,
cold
cold, cold, cold, cold
cold, cold, cold, It’s so cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, It’s so cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold,
so please,
—don't come near me
Who cares where
I am on this line
in order for me,
to be me...