There’s no flower in this world more beautiful than an artificial one.
That’s because everything is manufactured from lies.
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
antipathy world
The rain of despair pelts my umbrella and
Dampens my bangs and the hidden side of my heart
Oh, it’s all so troublesome
Before I knew it, the words had already withered
The fruit of the truth is ripening within me
Painting lies upon the mirror’s reflection,
a “makeup” of the loss of oneself
papapparapap
pararappappa
Let's play
a game
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
where we count all the riddles
tatattaratat
tararattatta
Why,
oh why
do we dance in this place?
I can’t understand even
the simplest of things
What even am I?
Even that,
stirred by the
hand of the night
love,
Just like
It disappears
I cried, still unable
to say even goodbye,
Phony
Tangled up in
lies, I am a
phony
Tangled up in
lies, I am a
phony
Tangled up in
lies, I am a
phony
Tangled up in
lies, I am a
phony
Tangled up in
lies, I am a
phony
Tangled up in
lies, I am a
phony
Tangled up in
lies, I am a
phony
Tangled up in
lies, I am a
phony
Tangled up in
lies, I am a
phony
(Interlude)
Before I knew it, the mimicked cries joined the unpleasant chorus
Their eyes, leery, are dissolving you
I am missing from the mirror’s reflection.
There is only a “fake” that everyone mistook for someone else
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
How do we live, as we crowd around
and lust after that thing known as love?
I’m swimming today again, as the night-train
is passing me by.
Dance the night away!
pa
papapparapap
pararappappa
Let us
sing
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
and deceive with riddles.
tatattaratat
tararattatta
Why,
oh why
does it hurt here so much?
I can't change these miserable days
This rain of despair just won’t let up
I cried, still unable to say even goodbye,
Phony
I’m just tangled up in lies
I can’t understand even
the simplest of things
What even am I?
Even that,
stirred by the
hand of the night
love,
Just like
It disappears
Goodbye, see you
later, I murmured
Phony
Tangled up in
lies, I am a
phony
Only the artificial flowers know
this secret phony.