Todoke kono omoi yo
Reach out, these feelings
The night sky is the runway to you
Yozora wa kimi e no kassouro
Ima sugu aitai yo I'm just crazy for you
I want to see you right now, I'm just crazy for you
Kizuitara utouto shiteta mitai
Before I knew it, it seems I had dozed off
Konna mayonaka hitorikiri
Alone in the middle of the night like this
Keitai nigirishimeteta te ni
With my phone tightly grasped in my hand
Nokoru chakushin kimi no namae
A lingering missed call, your name
Aitai,
Wanting to meet you,
Aitai, aenai,
Wanting to meet you, unable to,
Aitai, aenai, modokashikutte
Wanting to meet you, unable to, it's frustrating
Shiritai, furetai...
I want to know you, I want to touch you...
Kokoro ubatta no wa kimi nanda
It's you who has stolen my heart
Todoke kono omoi yo
Reach out, these feelings
Yozora wa kimi e no kassouro
The night sky is the runway to you
Haato o yurasu yo kimi no koe
Your voice stirs my heart
Onegai kore ijou jirasanaide
Please, don't tease me any longer
Kakehiki nante dekinakutte
I can't play games like this
Ima sugu aitai yo I'm just crazy for you
I want to see you right now, I'm just crazy for you