UNHAPPY?
A troubled human child
UNLUCKY?
For the inhumane
BE HAPPY!
Aim timelessly
Because you're alive
The past you tried to forget
And that boring future too
Counseling
Oh man
Anytime anywhere, peace, peace
UNHAPPY?
UNLUCKY?
BE HAPPY!
UNDEAD
Hey, hey,
Why do I somehow feel like I'm fighting?
I can't reach
I don't even want to reach
Myself, myself, myself, and myself from the past
I've been dead for a long time now
I fight with a transparent ghost
Deep in a childish and painful memory
Disappointed? It's gone
Oh? You like that better? That's ironic
Am I, as I am now, what's transparent?
Nonsense
A label that doesn't disappear
Yes! It's basically a complex
You seem to be possessed
The old me
That's wrapped up and
Won't leave
UNDEAD
I'm not dead yet
A chain of you and you
To be alive is to keep changing
Don't be satisfied
With unhappiness
You're a coward if you don't try to be happy
This world and this world are
A strange, strange fantasy
Will a demon appear next or will a snake?
The story finally begins after meeting
Is it a human or monster?
Whoops I digress, peace, peace
TL: MTBB