LAGTRAIN
hanarebanare no machi o
It seems the train connecting the far apart cities
tsunagu ressha wa itte shimatta ne
has already departed
nakushita kotoba o shiranai nara
If I don't know the words I lost,
poketto de nigirishimete
I'll grasp them tight from within my pockets
agaita iki o sutete
I wheeze out a pained breath as I sleep
nobiru kyou wa nemutte gomakase
and fake my way through this ever-lengthening day
nakushita kotoba o shiranai nara
If I don't know the words I lost,
kakueki teisha ni norikonde
I'll take a ride on the local train
yuugata to taikutsu no osasoi o kotowatte
I reject the evening, along with the invitations to boredom.
hitorikiri rojiura wa kesshite isoganaide
I'm all alone, I mustn't rush down the back alley
hora oudan hodou mo matte kure to itteru
Look, the traffic crossing is also saying “wait for me”
miharu machikado ga anata o hikitometeku
The street corner on patrol restrains you
hanarebanare no machi o
It seems the train connecting the far apart cities
tsunagu ressha wa itte shimatta ne
has already departed
nakushita kotoba o shiranai nara
If I don't know the words I lost,
poketto de nigirishimete
I'll grasp them tight from within my pockets
agaita yume o sutete
I wheeze out a pained dream as I sleep
yureru kyou wa nemutte gomakase
and fake my way through this ever-swaying day
nakushita kotoba o shiranai nara
If I don't know the words I lost,
akueki teisha ni norikonde
I'll take a ride on the local train
yuugata no eki no hoomu wa hidoku komiatte
The evening train station is terribly crowded
hitorijime dekiru made kyuukei shite hoshikute
I wanted it to take a break until I can have it all to myself
mata shuudan gekou ga
Again, a group returning
anata o sekashite iru
from school pushes you along
hora
Look,
jidou kaisatsu wa matte kure to itteru
the ticket machine is saying “wait for me”
fusagaru ryoute ga anata o hikitometeku
My occupied hands are holding you back
agaita yume o sutete
I wheeze out a pained dream
yureru kyou wa nemutte gomakase
as I sleep and fake my way through this ever-swaying day
nakushita kotoba o shiranai nara
If I don't know the words I lost,
kakueki teisha ni norikonde
I'll take a ride on the local train
hanareta machi to machi o tsunagu ressha ga
The train that connects the far apart cities-
yonda kaze ni tobasarenaide ite kure
Calls forth a wind, please don’t be blown away by it
nakushita kotoba wa sono mama de ii yo
The words I lost, it’s fine if you just let them be
yureru ressha ni mi o makasete hoshii kara
Because I want you to entrust your everything to this swaying train car
hanarebanare no machi o
The far apart cities-
It seems the train to the city
tsunagu ressha wa itte shimatta ne
of faraway farewells has already departed
nakushita kotoba o shiranai nara
If I don't know the words I lost,
poketto de nigirishimete
I'll grasp them tight from within my pockets
agaita iki o sutete
I wheeze out a pained breath as I sleep
nobiru kyou wa nemutte gomakase
and fake my way through this ever-lengthening day
nakushita kotoba o shiranai nara
If I don't know the words I lost,
kakueki teisha de tabi o shite
I'll set off on a journey, taking a ride on the local train
Music
inabakumori
Art & Animation
Nukunuku Nigirimeshi
Video
inabakumori
Recording assistance
Nukunuku Nigirimeshi
Translation source
AngelSubs
LAGTRAIN