As you like, My Pleasure
A frail oath was interwoven in my birth
Binding me to always chase the light
My mission showed me a miraculous joy,
Spinning many proud memories
I shall gift this world
A bouquet of thanks
Every star shining in the cosmos
A personal gift for you
Take your fate, your destiny
And please let them shine
My pleasure is being able to protect
Those still smiling
I've always longed for it, yearned for it
The thought of becoming stronger
I want even my whimpers
To be heard as beautiful song
Entrust your deepest sorrows to me
During these disorienting days
Subtitle source: YameteTomete
https://nyaa.si/view/1377372