And so,
Ka-kushite
Where, where, where shall we go?
Doko e doko e doko e mo tsuretette
A secret date
Hi-mitsu DEETO
Can you, can you, can you find me?
Kimi wa kimi wa kimi wa sagaseru kana?
Here I appear, wherever I go
Arawaru atashi wa yukusaki saki
I don’t think about what’s ahead
Ato saki zaki nara kangaenai
Clip-clop, clip-clop! Even the horse is surprised by the Pandora’s box
Pakara pakara! Uma mo bikkuri tamatebako
Get captivated quickly
Tettori hayaku toriko ni nare
After all, just having an acrylic stand isn’t enough, right?
Datte akusuta dake ja tarinai desho?
Not even for a moment, can’t get away—chomp!
Isshun tari tomo hanarenai gabu!
I love you, pop you
Ai rabyu poppyuu
Don’t look away
Yosomi shinai de ne
In the end, love is all that matters
Ai arawa ni kekkyoku wa
It’s only you!
Onryuu jan!
I appear everywhere I go
Yukusaki saki arawaru
Popular view
Poppyuraa byuu
Stay by my side forever
Zutto tonari de ne
Pop in from the pocket
Pokke kara POP IN
Sneaking in, Pop in 2
Shinobase POP IN 2
Knocked down and kicked around, Pop in
Fundari kettari POP IN
Hide and seek, boy
Kakuren BOY
Pop in from the pocket
Pokke kara POP IN
Sneaking in, Pop in 2
Shinobase POP IN 2
Boing! The Pop-in idol appears...
Pyon! Arawaru POP IN AIDORU......
POP IN Happy 2 U!
TL/Romanji: Thae(rin)