Subtitles: YouDeer
Alternative subtitles are available
Switch to English (Canada) to view them
Your media player does not support
the subtitle format used in this episode.
The subtitles will likely not display as originally intended!
Please make sure you're using a recent version of mpv,
which can be found at https://mpv.io.
For any further questions or inquiries,
we urge you to contact us on our Discord server.
• YouDeer team
Aw man...
This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or actual events is purely coincidental.
I took the long way 'round and now I'm late!
Hey, sorry I'm late...
Cut 1
Cut 2
Cut 3
Cut 4
A... A deer!
nun
bleat
plays
a
round
and
Ko
shi
stares
very
bo
dy
loves
to
watch
this
care
free
fawn
shi's
like
a
ti
ger
kee
ping
watch
since
dawn
tan!
nun!
Bleat!
dden
ly
a
deer
is
pre
sent,
tro
tting
'round
and
see
ming
plea
sant
ler-
wa
ving
is
a
ho
bby,
wait
a
sec,
school
girl
since
her
su
dden
trans
fer
e
very
bo
dy's
tal
kin'
'bout
seems
she
ain't
the
shar
pest
tool
in
the
shed?
They've
been
li
ving
all
'round
Ja
pan
since
sai!
If
you've
got
deer
cra
ckers,
I'll
take
Rein
deer
are
of
course
re
la
ted,
Se
row's
they're
fe
llow
un
gu
lates
with
e
ven
toes!
Come
and
do
a
blea
ting
dance
with
ning
a
rrives
one,
two,
three!
One,
two,
three!
nate
and
bleat
days
You
won't
know
what's
co
ming
in
these
deer-
brown
days
vant-
garde
is
what
we're
af
ter,
come
and
wreak
ha
voc
with
fore
I
knew
it,
I
was
a
ddic
ted
to
blea
ting
days
Through
wi
ld,
un
sta
ble,
cra
zy
deer-
brown
days
cchi
come
on!
Bring
on
the
ex
traor
thing's
out
of
reach,
a
ny
thing
goes,
When
I
see
your
smi
le,
it
makes
me
feel
great
deer?!
I
feel
as
if
it's
fate
when
I
look
in
your
eyes,
my
deer
Though
I
find
it
keeps
lant
state
we're
both
here,
the
fun
will
plays
a
round
and
Ko
shi
stares
tan!
tan!
New Student Bashame
Wh-Wh-Wh-Why the hell is there a deer in here?!
Well, I guess it wouldn't be
much of a deer club without one, but...
Thinking about it, they've always kinda been there.
How the heck did I not notice?
Quit eating those! They're for the deer club, not you!
Hey, Shikanoko! Did you bring this thing here?
Where is she?
Wh-What if this deer is...
Shikanoko!
Quit bucking around already!
I know you're hiding in there, Shikanoko!
Hurry up and turn back to normal!
She's not turning back?
Oh, is she mocking me or something?
She's got some nerve, I'll give her that.
Just watch, I'll make short work of her deersguise!
Take it off! Get that costume outta here!
Did you really think I was gonna
fall for such an obvious disguise?!
Oh goodness, I'm just parched!
Going between class and the clubhouse is exhausting.
Oh, that's right. I happened to
buy myself a little treat earlier.
Ta-dah!
The school store's seasonal special
that everyone's dying to try...
Sakura-flavored bubble tea!
Though I guess you can't drink it in that costume.
Ain't that a shame!
I even went to the trouble of buying you one.
Well, somebody's gotta drink it while it's still good.
Sure you don't want it?
I'm gonna drink every last drop.
Ignored?!
I thought the bubble tea plan would work for sure...
Molly!
Deer are herbivores.
They eat grass and plant leaves.
I worked so hard to raise him! I won't let you eat him!
The deer club has a multitude of houseplants.
Koshitan lovingly named and raised all of them herself.
Bob
Wendy
Spud
Let go of him, you damn deer!
Oh god, what's that noise? Are deer supposed to do that?
When bucks feel threatened,
they will begin to growl to ward off predators.
It's their way of saying, "keep your distance, or else".
Persistent, aren't you?
I won't back down either.
I've got to protect the lives of my plants!
That's it, you've forced my hand!
Just try getting past these! Your weakness, water bottles!
As you may recall, water bottles are Nokotan's greatest fear.
How's that? Ready to give in?
If you want me to free you,
you gotta take that costume off, capisce?
Whuuuh?
H-How did you...
You just stepped over them like it was nothing!
If I want my darlings to live a long and fulfilling life,
I have to think of something and fast.
If I were Shikanoko, what would tempt me? What would...
O-Of course!
Oh deer!
I-I can't believe I left my cringy notebook of poems here!
I better hurry up and burn this thing!
Le glance.
But I would hate for
my deer friend Shikanoko to feel left out.
If only she'd take that costume off and go back to normal,
I'd love to read some poems, just for her!
This book is so mind-bendingly cringe
that I can't even leave it at home,
and yet I'm showing it off to Shikanoko?
But my shame means nothing in the face of my darlings!
Bingo! She took the bait!
Now to reel her in...
I-I even wrote my own song just earlier.
Oh, how I'd love to sing it for Shikanoko!
Whassat? I wanna hear! I wanna hear!
Alright, alright, I'll sing a little of it.
And a one, two, three, four!
Do-do-do, cha-cha
Up and at 'em, former gangster Koshitan!
I can hear storms of sadness blowing loud
Could there be someone out there crying for me?
Woah-oh-oh-oh
In the empty halls, tiger's on the prowl
She's defending her territory
Her untouchable sanctuary!
Set foot in her lair and she'll tear you to shreds, yeah!
Stay right there
This tragic tale can't just end here,
So just sit tight and wipe the tears from your eyes
Good grief.
And here I was, trying to stay on the down-low.
Three minutes?
Three seconds is plenty.
Go! Fight! Koshitan!
Listen up, civvie kids, even though that's behind her
Never think she's gone soft!
Flaming fist, show me your strength
Shatter a cheekbone, set it ablaze!
A tiger's paw ain't so gentle.
If you're in trouble, then just call my name
Koshitan! Koshitan!
Woah-oh-oh-oh
Look who it is, former thug Koshitan!
Time for the second verse, same as the first!
Do-do-do, cha-cha
Up and at 'em, former gangster Koshitan!
Hate to say it, but that's all you're getting for now!
Aw, but I wanted to hear more.
Not a chance. Not until you get out of...
I wanna hear more!
Sing some more of Former Gangster Koshitan!
Wha... how...? Shikanoko?
Two Shikanokos? Wh-What in the world?
Huh? Two of me? Whaddya mean, Koshitan?
I'm talking about— That! There!
They're... talking?
He says he escaped from the Hino Zoo.
E-Escaped?
Maybe the smell of deer crackers led him here.
Oh, c'mon!
Anyway, what's this notebook of poems?
Woah!
Oh, and that song you were singing...
Keep singing it! Pretty please!
Up and at 'em, former gangster Koshitan!
In that moment, Koshitan would have given anything
for the ground to open up and swallow her whole.
Have a good antlernoon!
And the deer made its way back to Hino Zoo.
Mount Kinka
Koganeyama Shrine
Sanrikko Fukkō National Park
Mount Kinka
Student Orientation
The days are getting longer and
the cherry blossoms are in full bloom.
I'd like to congratulate our
new class of freshmen on joining us.
As a current student myself,
I extend you a warm welcome.
It's spring. Koshitan and her friends have become seniors.
People actually age here. This isn't Pokémon.
I really wanted to see your
student council address, Koshitan.
I bet it was cool.
Of course it was.
Oh my god! Are you okay?
What're you doing here?
What's wrong? Are you feeling sick?
Should we take you to the nurse?!
Do we call an ambulance?
Or the cops? The National Guard?!
Huh?
It was so warm and cozy here,
I must've fallen asleep.
Oh, okay then...
Who the heck?
Well, I'm glad you're feeling alright.
But what were you doing on our doorstep?
Judging by your uniform, you're a freshman, right?
I wanted to meet you in person.
What?
BA
SHA
ME
I'm Bashame Meme.
I'm a freshman.
I really look up to you, so I just had to meet you.
I asked Ms. Ukai, and she said
you'd probably be here, so here I am.
So she was stunned by my
model student-ness at the orientation,
and was just dying to meet me, huh?
I want to be like you one day.
So, um... Please take me on as your apprentice!
Sorry, but I must refuse, although I'm happy you...
Please, Shikanoko!
You're asking... Shikanoko?
Wh-Whazzat? Shikanoko? Not me?
Um, who are you, again?
I just gave a speech at the student orientation!
I'm the student council president!
I really wanted to meet Shikanoko,
so I was waiting here.
Is she a few sandwiches short of a picnic?
Bashame, why in the hell—
Why might you look up to her so much?
I'm glad you asked.
It all started before the orientation.
Student Orientation
I had collapsed in front of the school gates, y'see...
Wait, what?
So hungry.
I'm done for...
The orientation ceremony should be starting soon.
I'm gonna die here before
having even entered high school...
Want some?
Whuh?
Thank you so much.
See you, then.
W-Wait, hold on!
Um, what's your name?
I ain't got a name, kid. Just a deer passin' by.
Which brings us to now.
I'm deeply indebted to Shikanoko for her help.
Those crackers actually saved someone's life?
So, there I was at the orientation,
thinking to myself the whole time:
She was such a cool person.
I wanna be like her... I wanna be a deer like her!
You wanna be a deer?
So please, take me on as your apprentice!
Apprentice? Listen here...
Where did all those butterflies come from?!
Hey, what's your plan here?
Hey missy, your name was Bashame, right?
Yes, that's right!
Ya think yer prepared to be a deer like me?
What's with the voice?!
And how would she even become a deer?!
I am! I swear to give it my all
to become a deer like you!
What kinda pledge is that?!
First of all, y'gotta join the deer club.
Okay! I'll join the deer club!
Are you just going to keep ignoring
everything I'm saying here?
Koshitan is the president and caretaker of the deer club,
so you gotta say to her,
"Please take care of me", got it?
Roger that, Your Deerness!
Listen to the club president, dammit!
Wh-What now?
I've finally graduated middle school
and enrolled at the same high school as my sister!
I applied to join the Deer Club,
so now I can spend every day
from dusk to dawn with sister dearest!
We can do anything we want
without our parents knowing!
Sister deare—
Oh, Koshitan.
Won't you take care of me?
Q-Quit that!
Torako...
A-Anko?
Who is this girl you're fooling around with?
And so the deer club acquired two new members.
Mount Kinka,
Viewed from
Gobansho Mountain
Mount Kinka,
Viewed from
Gobansho Mountain
Well, that was hectic, but now we've got four members.
The deer club's finally shaping up!
I thought it would just end up as a do-nothing club,
but now we can really get off the ground!
Alright, gang! Let's get down to business!
Deer
Shikanoko
Noko
Senior
Self-proclaimed
Caretaker of
Koshitan
Koshi Anko
Freshman
Matching mugs with Torako!
—
More
than
Human
Less
than
Deer
Bashame
Meme
Freshman
Club
President
&
Deer
Caretaker
Koshi Torako
Senior
Oh, hell no!
The restructuring of the Deer Club has begun.
Deer Club
Meeting!
This marks the beginning of
the Deer Club's first plan-of-action meeting!
Deer Club
Meeting!
What's that?
She's so charming when she gets serious.
Order!
The year's just started and you're already lazing about!
Where's your pride in our Deer Club?
Was there ever any in the first place?
Time and place, Mr. Narrator.
This is downright depressing.
I put so much effort into this club and yet... look at us!
If people find out how lazy this club is...
they'll take away our funding and
kick me out of the presidency I worked so hard for!
I was pretty shocked to find out
Koshitan used to be a thug,
but I admire how straightforward
and to the point she is.
Everything about her is so adorbs!
Things need to change.
All of you are gonna decide on goals for the year!
Kaaaay.
First up, Shikanoko!
As the club's chief deer representative and
the only other senior present, tell us your goal!
Hmm, let's see, my goal...
Oh! My goal will be to take a deer cracker bath.
Rejected.
You didn't even hear me out.
I just know you'll waste all our funds on it!
Pick something else! Something more achievable!
Lessee then, something else...
Nope, nothing.
Aren't you the one who founded this club?
Didn't you have any plans?!
Ugh... she's a lost cause.
And a terrible example for the freshmen.
Alright, then the deer apprentice Bashame!
No making rice in the clubroom!
You want some, Koshitan?
Not at all!
You said you wanted to be a deer!
Don't you have any, like,
basic goals you want to accomplish?
Hm... lemme think...
I want to tend to a rice paddy!
What was that?
A... rice paddy?
Just a small one would be fine!
You lost me.
I've come to realize something.
In the harsh savannas of today,
one survival skill shines above all else.
And that skill is self-sufficiency!
So my plan is to start with
a rice paddy next to the clubhouse!
As a deer, I'll cultivate rice with the utmost care!
That's your goal?!
Get excited for episode 10.
Everyone's out of their damn mind...
Come on, Anko! You're the only one I can count on here!
My goal?
Well, now that I'm in the deer club
that you wanted to help out at...
I guess all I want to do is
stay by your side and support you.
A-Anko! That's my sister!
You're so reliable!
And then, if possible,
I want to make it so that you can't live without me.
Deer lord! Please go back to
the Anko from three seconds ago.
What are your goals, Koshitan?
Unlike you guys, I've actually
given mine plenty of thought!
So, what are they?
There's a lot, but first things first...
Yeah?
I want to spruce the clubroom up!
Haven't you done that already?
Think about it. This place used to be an old shed.
If we redecorate it and make it cuter...
Dont'cha think Koshitan's goal
has the least impact on our club?
Should the student council president
really be spending this much?
Sounds like we're shelving her idea for now.
Th-There's nothing wrong with
wanting our clubroom to look nice!
It's the club president's job to make it
livable for deer, wouldn't you say?
Then why won't you let me
take a deer cracker bath, huh?!
And what about my rice paddy?
And what about fooling around in the clubroom
without our parents knowing?!
Where did that come from, Anko?!
Plus, you've got it all wrong, Koshitan!
The point of the deer club is taking care of deer!
If you're gonna be my caretaker,
you have to do your part!
If this keeps up, my poor heart will have to move on!
What?!
Then there'll be no more deer in the deer club.
We'll have no choice but to disband...
No way...
It'll be all your fault for pushing us away, you know.
Seriously?!
You see now?
We're striking for better labor conditions,
like we used to have!
ENDEAR
YOUR DEER
What am I even supposed to say to that...
God damn it... Okay, what do you want me to do?
ENDEAR
YOUR DEER
Brush me.
ENDEAR
YOUR DEER
We always do that, though.
ENDEAR
YOUR DEER
Here.
ENDEAR
YOUR DEER
Brushing: Begin!
I see now!
Being brushed is essential to becoming a better deer!
I've already learned so much.
Nokotan's such a good mentor!
I don't think that's really related to brushing...
Koshitan! My head is also in need of brushing.
Do I have to?
I don't really care that much about you,
but if you're really that interested in
giving me a good brushing, I have no objections!
Stop putting words in my mouth!
I never said any of that!
You two... you things...
You don't know a thing about my sister's caretaking skills.
But of course, how could you?
We've been together for fifteen years.
It's me she should be brushing, not you.
That's right...
I have the potential to be the best deer
the deer club's ever seen!
When the heck did you become a deer?!
I thought you were my caretaker!
What do you think, sister dearest?
Why don't you give up those two pests
and brush me instead, hmm?
Well?
The pressure is crushing me...
Let's have a contest to see who can be the best deer!
Alright, bring it on!
I'm not gonna lose!
We're still in the middle of a meeting!
I am a deer!
A deer! Deer! Deeeeeer!
Hmm.
So this is the troublesome Deer Club.
Su
dden
ly
a
herd
of
deer
from
no
where
where
they
came
from
Deer
god,
oh
deer,
the
they're
all
a
round
Do
they
real
ly
love
the
taste
of
cra
ckers
that
much?
They're
thin
and
round,
baked
to
brown,
don't
just
be
a
tease!
Why
do
deer
seem
to
love
them
so
bad
ly,
though?
The
deer,
oh
my
deer!
May
be
deer
are
smar
ter
than
we
rea
lize!
Since
they
al
ways
seem
to
know
you've
got
them
Deer
god,
oh
deer,
the
they're
all
a
round!
Rain
or
shine,
at
a
ny
time,
they're
on
ly
for
the
deer!