Kasane Teto-san (11)
How do they find out so quickly?
Berated with threats like, "suffer the resonance!"
Q. Is updating to delete the meteor shower permitted?
Well, it's not wrong
To hell with salvation, that skin-deep melodrama
I take my orphan drugs-they're BAD
Q. Could you fully encrypt the god-awful look?
For a price
Kasane Teto-san (11)
Q. Could you fully encrypt the god-awful look?
For a price
Kasane Teto-san (11)
Forget common sense-let the brawl run amok
A band of loners playing idle games
Q. Sending it is too painful-can I cancel?
Don't make me laugh
How do they see it so quickly?
Why do they speak so frankly?
Why do I fall apart so easily, I wonder
PA-PARA
PARA PARA
Kasane Teto-san (11)
Why do I fall apart so easily, I wonder
PA-PARA
PARA PARA
Kasane Teto-san (11)
Nothing tops the near future
Today's shopping malls are online
It's complicity or death in the display window
Playing pinball with Monty Hall's expenses
A 100 minute oil massage, footbath included
~ Garnish with yuzu ~
Kasane Teto-san (11)
TE
TO
RIS
Why is this happening to me?
me?
Kasane Teto-san (11)
Putting off everything I'm neither interested in
nor serious about,
I, feigning ignorance of what I know, am hopeless
Let me erase the memories
of those who know my embarassing past
I've already apologized for causing trouble, okay?
Please, someone save me
Music and video
Hiiragi Magnetite
Art
Sena Yuuta
Lyrics translation
Bedrose
(Vocaloid Lyrics Wiki)
Are they so easily swayed by blind belief?
Are they so easily drawn to blind devotion?
I don't wanna know
TATARA
TARA TARA
I won't even look! I'm drawn in so easily-it's SAD
I've gone insane
full-time-it's MAD
I don't wanna go
I don't wanna go on living
Buh-bye!
Kasane Teto-san (11)
Extra holidays, laundry balls
Nightingale's let's play
That famous business card exchange scene
Playing Cee-lo highball in a bowl of debt
A hot-spring spree, 4 days and 3 nights, meals included
I wanna go ASAP
Kasane Teto-san (11)
TE
TO
RIS
I can't help but cringe
cringe
Kasane Teto-san (11)
Today, too, I'm too overwhelmed
by depression and mania to sleep
Someone, please, knock me unconcious STAT
Cancel my life-I'll be in the "canceled" club
I feel a vague sense of dread
It's my fault! I was wrong! I get it!
Kasane Teto-san (11)
No matter how much I care or how serious I am,
it's all in vain,
and even when I truly don't know, I'm called a liar!
I'm finished
Let me erase the memories
of those who know my embarassing past
I've already apologized for causing trouble, okay?
Please, someone save me
Kasane Teto-san (11)
I've already apologized for causing trouble!
Okay?! Please, someone, forgive me!
Kasane Teto-san (11)