The second I step outside, it’s all over
Despite the clear weather, I can’t proceed
The wind is just too strong, I’ll simply pass away
My hair is periodically, periodically swept back
Kyoufuu All Back
“I want to bury myself underground,”
is all I seemed to think
If this wind would go away,
it could be warm again
“I really want to sit down,”
is all I seemed to think
When I reluctantly set foot outside,
Pigeon, pigeon, pigeon, dove, a brawl has broken out
The second I step outside, it’s all over
Despite the clear weather, I can’t proceed
The wind is just too strong, I’ll simply pass away
My hair is periodically, periodically swept back
Kyoufuu All Back
The second I step outside, it’s all over
Despite the clear weather, I can’t proceed
The wind is just too strong, I’ll simply pass away
My hair is periodically, periodically swept back
The second I step outside, it’s all over
Despite the clear weather, I can’t proceed
The wind is just too strong, I’ll simply pass away
My hair is periodically, periodically swept back
My hair is swept back by the gale-force winds
Nothingness.
Kyoufuu All Back
Music
Yukopi
Animation
ozu
Singer
Kaai Yuki
Video
Yukopi
Translation
Bulbyblarp + MeaningfulUsername
(Vocaloid Lyrics Wiki)
Kyoufuu All Back
(Hair Swept Back By Gale-Force Winds)