Subtitles: DeerGod
Alternative subtitles are available
Switch to English (United States) to view them
This is a work of fiction. All the characters, places, and businesses shown are fictitious. Any resemblance to reality is purely coincidental.
I made it!
Deer!
Deer, deer, deer!
Deer?
Nyun
Shikanoko the careless doe has Koshi on her toes
Shikanoko the careless doe has Koshi on her toes (nyun nyun)
Doe eyes popping up here and there without a care
Antlers jamming out, and the body of a girl?!
It's the craze that's in the latest rumors
Let's see what you can do, greenhorn!
"They've been found in Japan since ancient times."
Deer crackers? I'll take a lifetime supply!
Reindeer are comrades, wild goats are bovines
but together, we're all even-toed ungulates!
Gracefully dancing the nyun step...
'Til the break of dawn!
One, two, three!
Even with a life of ruminating, nyunyunyun
you can never predict deer-tinted days!
Avant-garde is perfect, the chaos will only deepen!
You'll get hooked before you know it, nyunyunyun
on the chaos & nonsense of deer-tinted days!
Bring on the unprecedented!
Anything goes, there's no rules here
Your smile always fills me with energy
Are you my match, m-m-my deerest?!
While there's times you keep me on my toes,
I want to be with you forever!
Shikanoko the careless doe has Koshi on her toes!
DEER MEETS DARKNESS GIRL
Let's reacquaint ourselves.
This girl's name is Koshi Torako.
Secretly a former delinquent.
Burying away her past upon entering high school,
she established herself as an honor student,
and is now president of the student council,
as well as class rep. However...
A transfer deer (?) named
Shikanoko Noko saw through her disguise...
...and exposed her virginity.
Totally unrelatedly,
she was too easily persuaded...
...and was duped into becoming
the president of the mysterious Deer Club.
Now, once again,
we find her reluctantly going back...
All right! Time for Deer Club!
Perhaps not so reluctantly?
Well, it's not as if I'm
looking forward to going back...
Huh? So which is it?
I did a teensy-weensy bit of redecorating
for the club room this morning...
...and it turned out gorgeous!
But that doesn't mean I'm, like,
that excited for club time today...
...'cause I'm definitely not!
You don't say?
Besides, it's the president's job
to make the club room comfortable.
I can't wait to see her reaction!
Koshi-tan, you're amazing!
I had you all wrong!
Naturally!
All that's left is the wallpaper...
Oh! Maybe I'll get some shelves, too!
So much left to do!
Wait for me, my utopia!
THE DEER WILL PAY
Utopia is canceled until further notice.
Kumagorou!
Wh-What happened here?
Where's my utopia?
The utopia I poured my life savings and four hours
of back-breaking work into this morning...!
She woke up at 3:00 AM.
Koshi-tan, you okay?
It's dangerous over there.
Come here.
Was this you?!
Is this your doing?!
Did you ruin my utopia?!
Nyun? Whatcha talkin' 'bout?
It was already jacked up
when I got here.
Besides, it's not safe.
What do you mean?
Someone's out to kill me today.
Who? And why?
No idea.
But it's probably whoever
trashed our room.
On my way to school,
I fell down a five-meter-deep pitfall,
was pelted with spears
raining from the sky,
and even encountered
plastic bottles filled with water.
How are you even alive?!
Didn't you get speared in the head?!
And hold up, water bottles?
Even cats aren't scared of those anymore!
My antlers got totally
caught in the door, too!
You broke it again?!
Forget that!
I'm telling you, it's not safe here!
Get a grip.
Think about it.
There's no way anyone's after you.
You sure?
Of course.
Let's just step outside,
get some fresh air and think calmly—
Yo. You really gonna
blow cover like that?
This is a battlefield!
Who are you?!
Didn't I teach you being careless
is life or death out here?
You didn't teach me squat!
I was born in the peaceful Heisei era!
But hold on,
is someone seriously after you?
Seems so.
Tch. Screw this noise! I'm out!
What?! You'd abandon
your teacher and turn tail?!
Knock it off!
Since when am I your student?
I'm so over getting caught up
in this dumb cra—
Koshi-tan,
you all right in the head?
That wasn't an insult.
Who the hell are you?
Give me back my utopia!
Now she's mad!
You're going down!
I don't care if you're a soldier
or an assassin...
Bring it!
Crap! A grenade!
Huh?
Deer crackers?!
Hey! It's a trap!
You dimwitted dope!
Wait, wait, wait!
What is it, Koshi-tan?!
Open your eyes! It's a trap!
The trap to end all traps!
What kind of dummy
runs drooling right into a trap?
A trap...
Shikanoko?
Long, long ago, a deer was once asked...
"Why do deer eat deer crackers?"
Their answer?
"Because the deer crackers are there!"
Shikanoko!
I'm sorry, Koshi-tan...
But I love deer crackers
more than anything else in this world!
Yahoo!
Ah.
I goofed up.
I told you it was a tra—
I lost a little steam at the end there
and didn't reach the deer crackers!
You meant that?!
Hey! You over there
who has it out for me!
I know you can hear me!
My name is Noko-tan!
Reveal yourself!
I accept this battle fair and square!
Haven't you lost already?
The defeated deer
doth protest too much.
Oh, and bring me
more deer crackers, please!
Are you in any position
to be asking that?
You're awfully bold for roadkill.
Huh?
I had planned to be
rid of you sooner,
but I made some
unfortunate miscalculations.
I'll gladly do battle.
It will be a quick trip to hell for you.
This girl...
I've survived countless war zones,
but she easily captured me.
She's no amateur.
Who the hell are you?!
Anko?
What the heck are you doing here?
Sis!
I so missed you!
You missed me?
I would have seen you when I got home...
I wanna be with you every second, every minute,
24 hours a day, 365 days a year!
I can't get enough of your smell!
Can you, like, not?
And wait a sec,
why aren't you at school?
You're so cute when you're mad!
I wuv you!
Did you hear a word I said?
Koshi-tan, who's this?
Oh, my bad.
This is Koshi Anko.
My younger sister.
Koshi... Anko...
Like... smooth bean paste!
You must be picturing
something tasty, huh?
You're in for it now!
Never stare at me that way, pest!
Nyun?
Shikanoko Noko.
I'll never forgive you.
What's your issue with her?
Wait, was this all you?
Yes. I did it.
Why would you...?
It's all that deer's fault! All of it!
She's changed you!
You used to run home
straight for me after school!
To you? You mean where our family lives?
You've been coming home
so late recently...
I'm always home by seven!
I decided to follow you since
I wondered why you were out so late,
and found you cavorting with a deer
in some weirdo private club?! How obscene!
The only obscene thing here
is your reasoning!
Then you left so early
this morning to top it off...
You're only thinking about
your little deer love nest!
That comfy couch? Those adorable rugs?!
What are they doing in a club room?
Obscene! What were you two
planning on doing in there?!
W-Well...
She wanted to object,
but couldn't admit she had selfish motives.
You can't answer? Does that mean...
You slept together?
Of course not!
Are you psychotic?!
And what's with the kunai?!
Are you Iga? Kouga? Hokage?!
Hey, help me out here!
Koshi-tan is my woman!
Not helping!
Why are you running with it?
That's not what's happening here!
You'll never get Koshi-tan
no matter what kind of bean paste you are!
Now you've done it, dummy!
I knew it!
You stole my sister's virginity, didn't you?!
See?! I knew this would happen!
Do you realize how hard I've been
protecting my sister's virginity?!
I don't remember asking you for that!
This can't be forgiven...
The deer for taking my sister from me...
And my sister for
crossing a line with a deer.
I haven't crossed any lines!
Not even the Chuuou Main Line!
Setting: Hino City
I belong at your side...
Anyone who stands in my way
is my enemy...
So it's settled...
I'll destroy it all.
Anko...
I thought that if I ruined
this weirdo Deer Club of yours...
...and exterminated that pest,
my sister would return home to me.
But I've changed my mind.
Nyun.
You said something about
a fair and square battle, right?
Sounds fun.
I'll do battle with you.
But if I win,
you'll spend the rest of your life
as a deer at Nara Park.
Nara?
Of course, if I lose, I'll accept your
degenerate relationship with my sister...
...and graciously leave you alone.
Quit giving people the wrong idea!
Anko, get a hold of yourself.
This is ridiculous.
There's no reason to fight.
Why? It was the deer's idea.
Well, I guess that's true...
Fine. Let's battle.
Wait, are you serious?
If you become a Nara Park deer,
what will happen to the club?
Don't worry, Koshi-tan!
Huh?
Believe in me!
The Deer Club's bonds
go harder than deer crackers!
Shikanoko...
What the heck are you talking about?!
Deer crackers aren't hard!
They're thin and crispy!
But I have one condition, too!
What?
If I win the battle...
Please give me loads of deer crackers!
Just go to Nara already!
The Deer Club faces its first major crisis!
What will happen to the club? To Noko-tan?
The duel to decide the fate of
the Deer Club and deer crackers now begins!
I'll deport you to Nara Park like that!
All the deer crackers I can eat...
Can I leave now?
Big Shrine Gate,
Miyajima
Itsukushima Shrine,
1st Hinominami High School
Chitty Chitty King of Koshi Torako Competition!!
The first-ever Hinominami High School
Chitty Chitty King of Koshi Torako Showdown!
Let's introduce our two contestants!
What is going on here?!
Koshi Torako's younger sister
with an intense sister complex,
Koshi Anko-chan!
Does anything else in the world
matter besides my sister and I?
Hey, what's the deal here?!
The Deer Club's resident deer,
Shikanoko Noko-san!
I'll do whatever it takes
for those deer crackers!
Is anyone listening to me?!
How does it feel having these two
fight over you, Koshi-san?
I... I don't know what's happening...
You sound awfully excited!
Did you hear a word of what I said?!
And today's grand prizes are...
For Anko-chan, the right to deport
Noko-tan to Nara Park!
Deportation
Rights
And for Noko-tan,
a one hundred year supply of deer crackers!
Where'd those even come from?!
And I'm your host,
the advisor of the Deer Club, Ukai!
Do teachers have nothing better to do?
All right! Let's get started!
You put way too much effort
into this set...
Question one!
What does Koshi-san do every—
"What does Koshi-san
do every night before bed?"
Answer: She talks to the plushies in her room
and gives them each a goodnight kiss.
Correct!
Stop! What kind of question is that?!
Why are you violating my privacy?!
Is that wrong?
Of course it is!
But it's making your fans
go even crazier for you!
Koshi-san likes plushies?
Adorable!
Fan for life!
That's not the issue here!
Here's a picture to prove it!
My privacy! My privacy!
Please stop asking these questions!
Onto the second question!
You're ignoring me?!
Is Koshi-san currently—
Tch!
Noko-tan was quicker this time!
Your answer, please!
"Is Koshi-tan currently
not wearing a bra?"
The answer: She's wearing a bra top,
which isn't a real bra.
Again, what are these questions?!
Correct!
Y-You can't prove that without looking!
Schrödinger's bra.
Well then,
let's have a look at the footage!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Seriously!
Why do you have this footage?!
Question three!
Can I please leave now?!
Koshi-san has da—
"She has dated how many
boys or girls in total?"
Answer: Zero!
Uh, there could be someone,
you don't know that!
Not a soul.
Sorry! Incorrect!
Nyun?!
Koshi-san has dated
exactly zero boys or girls in total,
but why is that the case?
Please answer in twenty words or less.
Do you really need to dig that deep?!
Okay, Anko-chan!
Let's hear your answer!
Despite her peers forming relationships,
high school has been loveless...
...due to her shoujo manga mentality
of "awaiting true love".
Precisely twenty words.
Correct!
Quit analyzing me!
Her favorite manga magazine
is Bessatsu Friend.
Question four!
What incident from Koshi-san's
childhood has she been keeping secret?
She wet the bed until she was ten.
Correct!
Don't say that!
What thing does Koshi-san
surprisingly like?
Children's anime.
Correct!
Why is that surprising? Who cares?
Question five! What is Koshi-san's—
Egg on rice!
Correct!
How were you even able to answer that?!
Unbelievable!
The contestants are locked in a tie!
How much longer
will they violate my privacy?
This can't be right!
Why does this freaky deer
know so much about my sister?
There must be something more to this!
I know!
She's connected to the nationwide deer network,
Shika Shika Network (SSN)!
It's collecting my sister's data,
sending it to the supercomputer Shikagaku,
which then analyzes
and transmits it to her antlers!
It's about time I resorted to violence!
You let your guard down!
I had plenty more traps left!
So what was even the point of the quiz?
Koshi-tan's privacy was violated for nothing.
I'll riddle you with holes
before deporting you to Nara Park!
You can dodge them?!
What is up with this deer?
Take a hit already!
Take this! And this! And this!
I'm exhausted.
Why don't I just use this
as a smokescreen and bail?
You vermin!
Sis!
Shikanoko!
Hey, Shikanoko!
Koshi-tan... I feel... so sleepy...
What are you saying?!
Don't leave me, Shikanoko!
Open your eyes, Shikanoko! Shikanoko!
How could you...?
You follow me around, make me join your club...
Got me into this mess...
And now this...
Don't you dare go and
leave me all alone!
Lersant!
Nyun...
Shikanoko, you're alive!
I-I'm glad you're not dead, but how?
Earlier...
Nyun.
The crackers I picked up musta saved me.
Are we in some old-timey movie?!
Deer crackers aren't even hard,
they're thin and crispy!
Shikanoko...
Thanks for saving my sister.
I admit defeat.
I was so foolishly blinded
by hate and anger,
I almost hurt my own sister...
I'm a failure as a little sister!
You're the one
who should be by her si—
That's not true!
It's not true!
Because of you, miss— No...
Koshian, because of you, I was able to save Koshi-tan
with the deer crackers you gave me.
You saved her life!
We could be good friends,
don'tcha think?
May I call you... Noko-tan?
Huh?
Of course!
Huh...?
Take care of my sister
from here on out, okay, Noko-tan?
Leave it to me, Koshian!
Noko-tan! Koshian!
They're so lovely!
In the end, Koshi-tan couldn't process a single thing
that happened when all was said and done.
At least...
Starting tomorrow,
I'm wearing a bra every day.
The next day
It's white today.
You have x-ray vision?!
A bustling crowd of gathering deer
Where did they even come from, all these deer
Deer, deer, deer are all that's here!
Do those deer crackers really taste so great?
Round and golden brown, don't tease me with them...
Why ever would you really want them that bad?
Deer, deer, deer!
Are there smarts inside all those deer?
How come they always know if we have them?
Deer, deer, deer are all that's here!
Come rain, come sun, it's all for the deer