The story I'm about to tell you really happened
about six hundred years ago.
But I'd like you to listen as if it were fiction.
Because it happened too far in the past
to sound realistic,
and a story like this,
with no moral or happy ending,
is better off left as a lie.
About six hundred years ago, in a country whose name is long lost from history,
there was a very beautiful girl.
She was born as the sole daughter of wealthy nobility,
with beauty known to everyone in the country.
She was so beautiful that a portrait of her was displayed in every household.
Regardless of age, gender, or social status,
everyone was enthralled by her.
She was given a title from the emperor for her beauty alone.
Everyone in the country called her
"Beautiful Princess" and loved her.
Citizens formed long lines to the castle she lived in to get a glimpse of her rumored loveliness.
Each and every day, a mound of presents was placed in front of the castle.
"I turned your beauty into a song,
Princess. Please accept this."
A musician said thus and played his violin.
"I turned your beauty into a poem,
Princess. Please accept this."
A poet said thus and read his poem out loud.
"I turned your beauty into statues,
Princess. Please accept these."
An artist said thus and carved out a hundred statues.
But no gift would make the princess smile.
Nobody looks at me.
The princess lamented all alone in her room.
Beautiful this, beautiful that.
They all sing praises, but they say nothing more.
None of those people know what kind of person I am.
They don't know who I am on the inside.
That agonized the Beautiful Princess.
No matter what she did, no matter what she said,
the response was simply, "Beautiful."
Whether it be success or failure,
whether she did good things or bad,
the assessment she received was always the same.
Whatever she did was beautiful.
Asleep or awake, she was beautiful.
"Beautiful Princess" was a very apt description.
Such a beauty could only be called enchanting.
At this rate, it won't matter whether or not I have my own will.
My appearance does not hold dominion over me.
Beauty I just happened to be born into is nothing but a hinderance.
I would rather have them look at my soul than my looks.
Her great will, unspoiled by her own beauty, greatly touched the heart
of an old witch who had lived in that country for quite some time.
"Beautiful Princess, I will turn your beauty transparent, so that none can see it."
"Instead, I will make your heart visible to everyone around you."
"From now on, your soul will be what they judge."
The old witch cast a spell and waved her wand.
As promised, the clear skin of the princess became transparent.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
The Beautiful Princess gave thanks from the bottom of her heart.
Her outward beauty was gone,
but the princess's soul proved even more beautiful.
Word of her brilliance traveled all over the country without her even leaving her castle.
The princess's father felt shame for not noticing his daughter's beautiful soul for all that time,
and after greeting her in the morning,
he jumped off the balcony to punish himself.
The princess's mother was proud to have given birth to a daughter with such a wonderful soul.
She felt that such a feat was simply enough to end her role in the world
and peacefully passed away after eating breakfast.
The musician thought he could not possibly express the Beautiful Princess's kindness in song.
So he decided a suitable gift would be to offer what he held most dear, the thing he cherished more than life itself.
He chopped off his wrists—the things that allowed him to
play his instrument—and presented them to the princess.
The poet thought he could not possibly express the Beautiful Princess's wisdom in poetry,
so he decided a suitable gift would be what he held most dear, the thing he cherished more than life itself.
He ripped out his tongue—the thing that allowed him to
recite his poems—and presented it to the princess.
The artist thought he could not possibly express the Beautiful Princess's bravery in statues,
so he decided a suitable gift would be what he held most dear, the thing he cherished more than life itself.
He gouged out his eyes—the things that allowed him to
inspect his materials—and presented them to the princess.
All the citizens burned the portraits of the princess that they had long cherished.
They wondered why they took such great care of such trivial things for all this time.
While thinking reluctantly that it was not suitable as a gift at all,
they sacrificed their own lives,
the lives of their parents and siblings,
the lives of their children,
and the lives of their grandchildren.
It didn't take long before a mountain of presents—
or rather a mountain of corpses—
was stacked higher than the height of the castle itself.
Oh, what a tragedy!
I didn't think this would happen!
Losing all hope from the mountain of corpses and river of blood offered to celebrate her soul,
the princess sought out the old witch to have her magic dispelled.
But it was too late, as the old witch was the first one to see the princess's soul
and had already sacrificed her head,
which she cherished more than life itself and was filled with all the knowledge she gained over the years.
Seeing the old lady's severed head,
the princess broke down into tears.
A scene that evoked such pity, of her beautiful heart shedding tears for someone else,
further enchanted the citizens of the country.
They scrambled and raced to offer their lives, or perhaps what they cherished more than life itself, to the princess.
To console the princess, they smiled as they laid down their lives one after another.
The mountain of corpses that piled up,
or rather the castle made of corpses,
became infamous, and talk of it made its way across the capital and even to neighboring countries.
But all the armies that rushed over, upon seeing the radiance of the Beautiful Princess up close,
gladly, and willingly, became a part of the corpse castle.
I've had enough. Everyone is going to die.
But I can't save even one person.
If I but speak, if I but act, everyone will continue to die.
I want to die myself.
But she could not die.
The strength of the princess's will did not allow for that.
Nor was the princess permitted to fall into insanity.
"Then you shall embark on a journey."
That was when the old lady's severed head spoke up.
The tears that the princess shed had created a miracle.
The old lady came back to life for just one brief moment.
Someday, you may be able to save those who die for your beautiful soul that is beyond enchanting.
Until then, you must distance yourself from others.
Do not get close to anyone. You shall live alone.
With that said, the old lady passed away yet again.
And thus, leaving behind a castle stained scarlet with blood and a castle of corpses,
the Beautiful Princess embarked on a never-ending journey.
She followed the advice—or perhaps the curse—of the old witch.
So that no one else would meet their end.
A solitary journey to escape it all
where she was not allowed a single companion.
It would be a while yet before she turned into a vampire.
But the vampiric tale of the princess,
of Kiss-shot Acerola-orion Heart-under-blade—
the legend steeped in darkest blood—started there.
And her innocent soul finally, for the first time, saved a tiny life offered to her
in an incident roughly six hundred years later.
A Cruel Fairytale
The Beautiful Princess
UNHAPPY?
A troubled human child
UNLUCKY?
For the inhumane
BE HAPPY!
Aim timelessly
Because you're alive
The past you tried to forget
And that boring future too
Counseling
Oh man
Anytime anywhere, peace, peace
UNHAPPY?
UNLUCKY?
BE HAPPY!
UNDEAD
C-C-Cut-in!
For some reason
The future feels
Just so bleak and devoid of hope
I've been around for quite a while
Fed up with deja vu a la carte
There's not a hint of anything nice incoming
Such a shame
The years take their toll
Left with myths without substance and dull progress
I just want some excitement
I'm bored
I'm used to it all
Just kidding
Guidelines getting more detailed
Compliance getting more complicated
I feel the lid closing over me
Drain me dry
Lock stock and barrel
All taste the same
UNDEAD
I'm not yet dead
Watching you repeating you
Living means changing
Don't give up and settle for misfortune
It's not fair to give up striving for happiness
This world is a weird weird fantasy
Will a demon appear next or will a snake?
Encountering encounters starts the story
So is it human or a monster
But I digress, peace peace
Subtitles: MTBB