I sleep, with big problems weighing down on me
juudaina mondai kakaete nemuru
Though you can't beat that feeling of being loved, it's true
aisareta hou ga tashika ni musou tekidakeredo
When I awaken from cold dreams, my body feels numb
tsumetai yume kara mezamete shibireru
You shine so brightly, it could make me a shadow
karada chuu ga mabushiikara watashi wa kage ni nareru
It's time to take that step
iza fumikome
Though there's nothing certain about it
tashikana koto nado hitotsu mo naikeredo
It carries my childish heart into tomorrow
osanai kokoro o asu ni hakobu nosa
It's time to blast out the thoughts rattling around in my brain
aa karakara sawagu shikou tobashite
And live, to its fullest, a life
maegari shiteru kono inochi o
I've been taking advances on for so long
tsukaikiranakucha ima kono toki mo
But I also love the days I spend lying around, doing nothing
daradara sugiru hi mo aishite
So I know I'm going to go see you
kitto kimi ni ai ni yuku
Before it all ...
itsuka kieteshimau ...
... disappears some day
... mae ni
Subtitle source: neoHEVC
https://nyaa.si/view/1678808