MAMMA MIA
ABBA
Covered by: Austin Weber
MAMMA MIA
ABBA
Covered by: Austin Weber
I've been cheated by you
since I don't know when
3...
2..
1.
I've been cheated by you
since I don't know when
So I made up my mind, it
must come to an end
Look at me now, will I ever
learn?
I don't know how, but I
suddenly lose control
There's a fire inside my soul
Just one look and I can hear
a bell ring
One more look and I forget
everything, whoa
Mamma mia, here I go again
My, my, how could I resist
you?
Mamma mia, does it show
again?
My, my, just how much I
missed you?
Yeah, I've been
brokenhearted
Blue since the day we
parted
Why, why did I ever let you
go?
Mamma mia, now I really
know
Why I could never let you go
I've been angry and sad
'bout the things that you do
So I made up my mind and
told you that we're through
But when you go, when you
slam the door
I think you know that I won't
be away too long
You know I'm not that
strong
Just one look and I can hear
a bell ring
One more look and I forget
everything, whoa
Mamma mia, here I go again
My, my, how could I resist
you?
Mamma mia, does it show
again?
My, my, just how much I
missed you?
Yeah, I've been
brokenhearted
Blue since the day we
parted
Why, why did I ever let you
go?
Mamma mia, even when I
say
Bye-bye, take me now or
never
Mamma mia, it's a game we
play
Goodbye doesn't mean
forever
Yeah, I've been
brokenhearted
Blue since the day we
parted
Why, why did I ever let you
go?
Mamma mia, now I really
know
Why I could never let you go