MAMMA MIA
ABBA
Covered by: Austin Weber
MAMMA MIA
ABBA
Covered by: Austin Weber
I've been cheated by you since I don't know when
3...
2..
1.
So I made up my mind, it must come to an end
Look at me now, will I ever learn?
I don't know how, but I suddenly lose control
There's a fire inside my soul
Just one look and I can hear a bell ring
One more look and I forget everything, whoa
Mamma mia, here I go again
My, my, how could I resist you?
Mamma mia, does it show again?
My, my, just how much I missed you?
Yeah, I've been brokenhearted
Blue since the day we parted
Why, why did I ever let you go?
Mamma mia, now I really know
Why I could never let you go
I've been angry and sad 'bout the things that you do
So I made up my mind and told you that we're through
But when you go, when you slam the door
I think you know that I won't be away too long
You know I'm not that strong
Just one look and I can hear a bell ring
One more look and I forget everything, whoa
Mamma mia, here I go again
My, my, how could I resist you?
Mamma mia, does it show again?
My, my, just how much I missed you?
Yeah, I've been brokenhearted
Blue since the day we parted
Why, why did I ever let you go?
Mamma mia, even when I say
Bye-bye, take me now or never
Mamma mia, it's a game we play
Goodbye doesn't mean forever
Yeah, I've been brokenhearted
Blue since the day we parted
Why, why did I ever let you go?
Mamma mia, now I really know
Why I could never let you go