UNHAPPY?
A troubled human child
UNLUCKY?
For the inhumane
BE HAPPY!
Aim timelessly
Because you're alive
The past you tried to forget
And that boring future too
Counseling
Oh man
Anytime anywhere, peace, peace
UNHAPPY?
UNLUCKY?
BE HAPPY!
UNDEAD
C-C-Cut-in!
For some reason
The future feels
Just so bleak and devoid of hope
I've been around for quite a while
Fed up with deja vu a la carte
There's not a hint of anything nice incoming
Such a shame
The years take their toll
Left with myths without substance and dull progress
I just want some excitement
I'm bored
I'm used to it all
Just kidding
Guidelines getting more detailed
Compliance getting more complicated
I feel the lid closing over me
Drain me dry
Lock stock and barrel
All taste the same
UNDEAD
I'm not yet dead
Watching you repeating you
Living means changing
Don't give up and settle for misfortune
It's not fair to give up striving for happiness
This world is a weird weird fantasy
Will a demon appear next or will a snake?
Encountering encounters starts the story
So is it human or a monster
But I digress, peace peace
TL: MTBB